<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><modules><module><id><![CDATA[685]]></id><name><![CDATA[productmedia]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Product Media (Audio / Video)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Видеоролики и Музыка]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[ ﻿]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/videos-music/685-product-media-audio-video.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/685.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[ ﻿]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Make your product pages more interactive and your products more accessibleGive more information on your products: benefits, a better description, recommendations for use, etc.Easily increase your conversion rateBoost your sales and reduce the return rate of your products]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.2.7]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[44.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[34.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/611425-pprod/product-media-audio-video.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/611425-pbig/product-media-audio-video.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[1015]]></id><name><![CDATA[pm_advancedpack]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Advanced Pack 5]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Перекрестные продажи и Создание комплектов]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Продажа пакетов товаров с учетом наличия на складе и возможность проводить бизнес-операции]]></description><author><![CDATA[Presta-Module]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/cross-selling-product-bundles/1015-advanced-pack-5.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/1015.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Продажа пакетов товаров с учетом наличия на складе и возможность проводить бизнес-операции.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Возможность&nbsp;закупать&nbsp;дополняющие друг друга&nbsp;товары со скидкой или без нее одним нажатием  Хотите увеличить среднюю корзину и при этом позволить своим клиентам экономить, если они приобретают несколько товаров одновременно? Теперь это возможно благодаря модулю&nbsp;Advanced&nbsp;Pack! Вы сэкономите время, сможете создать пакеты товаров, которые можно будет купить всего одним нажатием, и вам не придется беспокоиться о наличии на складе или о дополняющих товарах.  Дополнительный ценный инструмент продаж Помогайте своим клиентам совершать покупки. Предлагайте им&nbsp;пакеты дополняющих товаров,&nbsp;которые вы составите заранее, так же как это делают продавцы в обычных магазинах. Например, этот замечательный фотоаппарат, карта памяти и треножник.&nbsp;Очевидно, что&nbsp;эти товары дополняют друг друга, и это заинтересует клиентов.  Или можете выставлять товары, которые продаются лучше всего, вместе с теми, которые менее популярны, чтобы клиенты увидели их.  В ваших пакетах может быть сколько угодно товаров, но не менее двух. Выберите количество каждого товара, а затем дополняющие товары на свой вкус. Вариантов приумножить возможности масса.  Хотите отложить покупку определенного товара из пакета? Это тоже возможно! Таким образом, вы сможете&nbsp;предложить бесплатный товар,&nbsp;если он будет приобретен в составе пакета. Возможностей множество! Встроенный помощник Не всегда очевидно, какие именно&nbsp;товары стоит включать в пакет. И здесь опять же вам поможет модуль&nbsp;Advanced&nbsp;Pack. При создании пакета модуль будет предоставлять вам такие важные сведения, как количество проданных товаров или их наличие на складе. В ваш пакет также встроен&nbsp;динамический симулятор цен,&nbsp;который поможет лучше понять, когда стоит совершить сделку, не навредив прибыли. Станьте экспертом по дополняющим товарам  Один из добавленных в пакет&nbsp;товаров доступен в нескольких цветах, но вы не хотите предлагать их все в одном наборе? Вам поможет модуль&nbsp;Advanced Pack.  Вы также сможете заранее продумать дополняющие товары по умолчанию для каждого товара пакета, даже если они отличаются от указанных в вашем каталоге.  Тогда ваши клиенты смогут&nbsp;выбрать то, что им захочется,&nbsp;среди параметров, которые вы включите в предложение.  Бизнес-мотивация  Мотивация&nbsp;&mdash; это то, что побуждает вашего&nbsp;посетителя сделать покупку. Главная задача&nbsp;&mdash; убедить как можно больше посетителей оформить заказ, и/или&nbsp;чтобы они&nbsp;потратили больше денег за сделку. Возможно, вы уже пробовали предлагать бесплатную доставку при определенной стоимости покупок и скидки на определенные товары или даже рассылали скидочные купоны? Все эти методы работают, но их возможности ограничены, так как эти акции временны из-за чрезмерных затрат! Хватит искать, решение уже нашлось!  Для стимулирования покупок модуль&nbsp;Advanced&nbsp;Pack&nbsp;предоставит выбор по применению скидки, когда все&nbsp;товары в корзине будут заказаны, что побудит клиентов приобрести весь пакет.  Доступны 3&nbsp;возможности:Предложить определенную скидку&nbsp;на каждый товар&nbsp;из пакета.Применить общую скидку на&nbsp;набор&nbsp;товаров.Применить&nbsp;фиксированную цену,&nbsp;учитывая психологию покупателей например.Модуль&nbsp;Advanced Pack&nbsp;также позволяет управлять скидками, которые уже были применены к вашим товарам. Таким образом, вы сможете учесть их в цене пакета или, наоборот, вычесть, чтобы выбрать заранее заданную скидку на пакет. Принимать решения будет еще проще благодаря&nbsp;четкому и интуитивно понятному интерфейсу, найти товары со скидкой в котором не составит труда.  Больше не придется переживать о несовпадающих ценах  Приходилось ли вам когда-нибудь пересматривать все цены в каталоге, чтобы выявить и исправить возможные несовпадения? Что если бы вам пришлось вручную устранять последствия изменений в ценах товаров из пакетов? Если это не было запланировано в ваших решениях по управлению пакетами, то стало бы значительной сверхурочной нагрузкой! Напоминаем, что с помощью модуля&nbsp;Advanced Pack&nbsp;можно решить эту проблему. По умолчанию, если цена пакета не была снижена, то она складывается из цен входящих в него товаров. Как только вы измените цену товара после создания пакета,&nbsp;цена пакета изменится автоматически&nbsp;без вашего участия. В тех случаях, когда вы примените скидку на один или более товаров из существующего пакета, при условии что вы имеете права на такие&nbsp;рекламные изменения, цена за пакет будет также изменена, а клиенты увидят, какая была применена скидка.  Товар из вашего пакета подпадает под экологический налог? Нет проблем&nbsp;&mdash; это будет автоматически четко указано в цене пакета в полном&nbsp;соответствии с законодательством. Все, что касается управления вашим складом, автоматизировано! Каждый заказанный пакет будет&nbsp;автоматически убран&nbsp;со склада, на котором хранился. Таким образом, вы избежите двойной проверки складов и проблем, связанных с несоответствием количества. Кроме того, когда&nbsp;товара из пакета не окажется на складе, он&nbsp;будет автоматически отображаться как недоступный&nbsp;для покупки, благодаря новейшей системе предупреждения о наличии.  Для ваших клиентов мы внедрили наглядную удобную систему, которая сразу же оповещает о малом количестве дополняющих товаров или&nbsp;товаров, входящих в пакет.&nbsp;Будьте уверены: никто не закажет&nbsp;товары, которых нет&nbsp;на складе!  Выделите пакеты и продайте больше После того как вы оформите пакет, вы сможете настроить его так же, как и классический товар. Можно выбрать для него любое изображение, внести его в любую категорию,&nbsp;оптимизировать для поиска, добавить описание, присвоить EAN-код или определенный номер, задать объем для расчета стоимости доставки и не только.  Для сжатого представления и для более эффективной рекламы модуль&nbsp;Advanced Pack&nbsp;автоматически отобразит все фотографии&nbsp;товаров пакета, а также их табличные описания. Ваши клиенты получат нужную информацию, не покидая страницы пакета, и&nbsp;смогут оформить покупку одним нажатием.  Но это не все... Для большей наглядности ваши пакеты будут автоматически&nbsp;выделяться в описаниях, если&nbsp;продаются партиями. Таким образом, вы побудите клиентов заказать пакет&nbsp;целиком&nbsp;вместо одного товара, который они собирались приобрести. По большому счету, это&nbsp;сопутствующие продажи: доступный способ&nbsp;увеличения средней покупательской корзины! Мы позаботились и о дизайнерах  Изначально мы позаботились о том, чтобы этот модуль могли без труда приспосабливать как веб-агентства, так и дизайнеры либо специалисты по интеграции. Модуль прекрасно приспосабливается к темам по умолчанию PrestaShop 1.5 и 1.6, предоставляя при этом наиболее расширенные возможности графической настройки. В состав модуля входят набор шаблонов JavaScript и таблиц стилей CSS, которые повысят эффективность&nbsp;внедрения. Таким образом, вы или специалист по интеграции можете пользоваться полными возможностями движка&nbsp;Advanced Pack&nbsp;5, чтобы графически воплотить то, что будет в лучшей мере соответствовать общему стилю вашего интернет-магазина.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[merchandizing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[5.2.7]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.1.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[249.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[289.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[224.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Oфициальный cоздатель модулей"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/616235-pprod/advanced-pack-5.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/616235-pbig/advanced-pack-5.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[1048]]></id><name><![CDATA[facebookpsshoptab]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Advanced Shop for Fan Page]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Товаров в социальных сетях]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Create a multilingual and completely customized Facebook shop]]></description><author><![CDATA[Business Tech]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/products-social-networks/1048-advanced-shop-for-fan-page.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/1048.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Create a multilingual and completely customized Facebook shop]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[* * * WINNER OF THE 2011 PRESTASHOP AWARDS CEREMONY FOR THE BEST MODULE * * * Stand out from the competition and present your products on Facebook in a completely customized shop tab that will differ from the shop tab natively offered by Facebook and used by many merchants.(x) Effective way to increase your sales, the "Facebook shop" has become essential in the e-commerce area. It allows you to display your products in sale on your site directly on the most popular social network. Then, you make the most of your Facebook community to boost the traffic on your PrestaShop site. Contrary to the native shop tab, that has many constraints, the "Advanced Shop for Fan Page" module allows you to: create a completely customized Facebook shop, whether in terms of design, menu type or displaycreate a multilingual and multicurrency shopnot need to submit your products to Facebook for review in order to make them visible for the publicmake the PrestaShop website's modifications instantly visible on the Facebook shop (changes of price, product image,...)display featured categories on the home pagedisplay on Facebook the average rating of each product/category, given on your site (with the shape of stars) if you also have installed on your Prestashop our product rating "Customer Ratings and Reviews Pro + Google Rich Snippets" module (available here: https://addons.prestashop.com/en/seo-natural-search-engine-optimization/6144-customer-ratings-and-reviews-pro-google-rich-snippets.html)  Notes: (x) 1/ So that real-time harmonization between Facebook and your online store is possible, the module has to create a new custom "shop" tab, independent of the default "shop" tab already installed by Facebook on your page. 2/ if you want to create Facebook catalogs and tag your products on Facebook and Instagram, you should choose our "Dynamic Ads + Pixel" module instead, that is available here: https://addons.prestashop.com/en/remarketing-shopping-cart-abandonment/23671-dynamic-ads-pixel.html. 3/ Facebook mobile app does not allow custom tabs insertion, like the one created by our module. Therefore, this latter can only be displayed on the Facebook web version. If you want to see your Facebook shop on mobile, you have to choose our "Dynamic Ads + Pixel" module (available here: https://addons.prestashop.com/en/remarketing-shopping-cart-abandonment/23671-dynamic-ads-pixel.html) in order to import your products into the native Facebook shop tab (however you will not be able to customize the shop).  To know more about the difference between the Facebook native shop tab (and filled by our "Dynamic Ads + Pixel" module) and the custom tab set by our "Advanced Shop for Fan Page" module, read our detailed comparison at this address: https://faq.businesstech.fr/en/faq/230  ]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[social_networks]]></tab><version><![CDATA[5.2.6]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.3.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[79.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[89.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[74.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Oфициальный cоздатель модулей"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/963149-pprod/advanced-shop-for-fan-page.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/963149-pbig/advanced-shop-for-fan-page.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[1768]]></id><name><![CDATA[gmerchantcenter]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Google Merchant Center (Google Shopping)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Сравнение цен]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[The most advanced Google Merchant Center module to upload your products to Google Shopping and get thousands of new, highly qualified visitors on your online shop]]></description><author><![CDATA[Business Tech]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/price-comparison/1768-google-merchant-center-google-shopping.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/1768.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[The most advanced Google Merchant Center module to upload your products to Google Shopping and get thousands of new, highly qualified visitors on your online shop.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Upload your products to Google Shopping and get thousands of new, highly qualified visitors on your online shop.&nbsp;The performance of Google AdWords Shopping campaigns and your presence in the &quot;Shopping&quot; results of Google&#39;s search engine largely depends on the quality of your Google Merchant Center feed and completeness of your data. The more information accurate you include, the better the results ! This very complete module will let you achieve just that and maximize your chances of obtaining good rankings on Google Shopping, while minimizing the time you will need to spend to have all your products accepted by Google.&nbsp;Instantly boost your traffic : Google Shopping and AdWords benefit from hundreds of millions of hits each month. Moreover this traffic is highly targeted and brings qualified visitors to your shop&nbsp;Increase your sales and ROI : Because traffic is extremely targeted, Google Shopping and Google AdWords Shopping Campaigns provide you with one of the highest return on investment rates compared to other marketing channels and is very cost effective&nbsp;About your products export, the power of the module allows you to only focus on the configuration of a single product feed (a primary feed) and not to waste time with the configuration of &quot;supplemental feeds&quot; and numerous &quot;rules&quot; provided by Google. You modify your product information directly in the module and you have the possibility to automate the update of all your data in Google Shopping, daily.&nbsp;Present in over 37 countries as of today, Google Shopping is a fast track start for international expansion&nbsp;&nbsp;With more than 6000 copies sold, 510+ reviews and an average 4.7/5 rating, our Google Merchant Center (Google Shopping) module is hands down the most robust, accurate, powerful and complete module for Google Shopping.&nbsp;We also have extensive knowledge and experience on the ins and outs of Google&#39;s rather complex requirements, and our tech support team will gladly help answer your questions to the best of their ability !&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;For power users and SEM agencies, for even more great features, including advanced custom labels management, promotions feed and quick inventory feed, you may be interested in purchasing the PRO version of the module available on&nbsp;https://addons.prestashop.com/en/price-comparison/20908-google-merchant-center-pro-google-shopping.html&nbsp;&nbsp;This module is developed and published by Business Tech, certified PrestaShop developer and winner of the&nbsp;2011, 2014 and 2017 PrestaShop Awards for &quot;Best module&quot;, with over 7 years of experience working with Google and Facebook. You are guaranteed to buy a robust, reliable and quality module.&nbsp;Furthermore, at Business Tech, we have a fast and efficient tech support&nbsp;: when you contact us, you are talking directly to the developers, so you are sure to be well informed !&nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[smart_shopping]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.7.18]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[119.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[134.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[109.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Oфициальный cоздатель модулей"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/963144-pprod/google-merchant-center-google-shopping.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/963144-pbig/google-merchant-center-google-shopping.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[2072]]></id><name><![CDATA[pm_advancedtopmenu]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Advanced Top Menu - Responsive]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Меню]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Advanced Top Menu&nbsp;позволяет построить все типы горизонтальной навигации: одноуровневая панель, выпадающие меню, богатое меню, мега меню с колонками]]></description><author><![CDATA[Presta-Module]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/menu/2072-advanced-top-menu-responsive.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/2072.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Advanced Top Menu&nbsp;позволяет построить все типы горизонтальной навигации: одноуровневая панель, выпадающие меню, богатое меню, мега меню с колонками.﻿]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Advanced Top Menu&nbsp;упростит навигацию по сайту и простоту его использования.&nbsp;Advanced Top Menu&nbsp;предлагает полный обзор Вашего каталога, чтобы покупателю было проще найти нужный ему товар.&nbsp;Благодаря его модульному построению, Вы сможете использовать строку меню для отображения картинок, действующих скидок, а также рекламы предоставляемых Вами услуг.&nbsp;&nbsp;Снабженный интерфейсом, который позволяет управлять строкой меню, не имея специальных технических знаний:&nbsp;ResponsiveНеограниченное количество закладокНеограниченное количество колонок&nbsp;Неограниченное количество&nbsp;﻿элементовПолная упрощенная графическая поддержкаАвтоматическая поддержка меню из Вашего каталогаВсе типы содержания: Категории, Производители, Поставщики, CMS, Таможня...Информация отображается в зависимости от статуса пользователя&nbsp;A faster and cleaner configuration&nbsp;interfaceNew default&nbsp;theme for optimal&nbsp;design out of the boxNew appearance settingsNew specific settings for mobileA&nbsp;Sticky mode, which let your menu always visible regardless of scroller&nbsp;positionAllows you to restrict the display of some elements for desktop or mobile viewAllows you to add different images for each languageOpening animation effect on submenusDelay on opening submenusContextual help tips in Back Office]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.12.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[59.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Oфициальный cоздатель модулей"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/573526-pprod/advanced-top-menu-responsive.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/573526-pbig/advanced-top-menu-responsive.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[2376]]></id><name><![CDATA[prestagiftvouchers]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Coupons / Discount vouchers]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Обеспечения лояльности покупателей и акций "Приведи друга"]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[ &nbsp; &nbsp;]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/referral-loyalty-programs/2376-coupons-discount-vouchers.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/2376.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[ &nbsp; &nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[With the Loyalty&nbsp;Discount Vouchers module you can:  &nbsp;Automatically create cart rules that generate offer codes emailed to your customers,&nbsp;Customize the coupons&rsquo; name, their value as a percentage or amount as well as their validity period,&nbsp;Increase average cart size on your site by defining minimum purchase amounts in order to use the discount voucher,&nbsp;Build customer loyalty by encouraging customers to buy again from your store,&nbsp;Easily liquidate your inventory of products of your choice, and better promote your new products and categories]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[advertising_marketing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.3.7]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[59.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[69.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[49.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/708607-pprod/coupons-discount-vouchers.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/708607-pbig/coupons-discount-vouchers.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[2501]]></id><name><![CDATA[amazon]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Amazon Market Place]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Торговая площадка]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Best-seller and exclusive on PrestaShop Addons, the Amazon Market Place module is the #1 solution to export products on Amazon, import and manage orders from the marketplace]]></description><author><![CDATA[Common-Services]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/marketplaces/2501-amazon-market-place.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/2501.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Best-seller and exclusive on PrestaShop Addons, the Amazon Market Place module is the #1 solution to export products on Amazon, import and manage orders from the marketplace.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[You can easily integrate your PrestaShop store to the world&rsquo;s top marketplace and significantly increase your sales. You import your orders into your PrestaShop store and centralize your stocks.  Managing your inventory efficiently and quickly honoring your Amazon orders allows you to increase the degree of customer satisfaction and thus automatically increase the rank of your seller performance.  The design of the module is based on the initial experience of online retailers. The module was developed by an online retailer for the service of his colleagues and it was developed by a team of professional developers, by making it easy to use and to have the maximum efficiency.  Your purchase is protected by free technical support that is provided unconditionally until the products are placed online and the first orders are imported.  This module was developed by Common-Services, which is a partner agency of Prestashop. Common-Services has been featuring on PrestaShop Addons&nbsp; since 2010 and it has also published 15 other best-selling modules that are marketed only on PrestaShop Addons.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[market_place]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.4.124]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.6.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[199.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[224.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[179.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge><badge label="Oфициальный cоздатель модулей"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/686436-pprod/amazon-market-place.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/686436-pbig/amazon-market-place.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[2659]]></id><name><![CDATA[protectmyshop]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Protect My Shop / Protéger Ma Boutique]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Безопасности и доступа]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[This module developped by LIBRASOFT gives you the best protection for your shop against thiefs and hackers. You can parameter in your back office up to 9 scripts of protection]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/website-security-access/2659-protect-my-shop-proteger-ma-boutique.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/2659.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[This module developped by LIBRASOFT gives you the best protection for your shop against thiefs and hackers. You can parameter in your back office up to 9 scripts of protection. &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[This module developped by LIBRASOFT gives you the best protection for your shop against thiefs and hackers. You can parameter in your back office 9 scripts of protection. &nbsp; In the back-office of the module, you can activate / unactivate one by one the protection scripts. The protection is totally personalizable, activating or not some protections, but even some specific rules of these&nbsp;protections.  You will be protected against all types of injection :SQL InjectionsXSS InjectionsSHELL Commands InjectionsCode InjectionsCGI Injections You will be protected against data thief :Hotlinking protectionFiles protectionCopy-Paste protectionRight Clic protection No surprise, you can adapt the protections to your needs easily through the multiples available tabs of personalisation. &nbsp; Your shop protection has no price. Protect My Shop Module is the better protection module ever developped for PrestaShop.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.3.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.6.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[149.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[169.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[134.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Best Module Time Saver"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/awards-savetime.png]]></badge><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/668741-pprod/protect-my-shop-proteger-ma-boutique.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/668741-pbig/protect-my-shop-proteger-ma-boutique.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[2778]]></id><name><![CDATA[pm_advancedsearch4]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Advanced Search 4]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Поиск и фильтры]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Выпущена новая версия лучшего многофункционального модуля навигации для PrestaShop! Победитель  Best Module Awards]]></description><author><![CDATA[Presta-Module]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/search-filters/2778-advanced-search-4.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/2778.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Выпущена новая версия лучшего многофункционального модуля навигации для PrestaShop! Победитель  Best Module Awards]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Приложение для интернет-магазинов, которые предлагают широкий спектр товаров. Advanced Search 4 позволяет добавить любое количество поисковых систем и расположить их в любом месте страницы. Процесс поиска модуля основан на заданных фильтрах. Фильтры позволяютразнообразную и удобную навигацию. Они помогут Вашим клиентам найти продукты, которые соответствуют их критериям запроса, за минимальное количество кликов. Advanced Search 4 разрабатывался для того, чтобы исполнять запрос в кратчайшие сроки, даже для каталогов, которые содержат несколько тысяч продуктов или категорий. Первая версия опубликована в 2010 году - Победитель  Best Module Awards в 2012 - Лучшие продажи по мнению Addons с 2010 года. Вы можете выбрать из 3 типов поисковых систем:Поиск по всему каталогу:Поиск по выборке продуктов: поиски ведется по странице, на которой находится пользователь.Поэтапный поиск: критерии поиска уточняются и воспроизводятся, пока пользователь формулирует свой запрос. Помимо своей основной функции, модуль Advanced Search также известен как  один из лучших решений для индексирования. Он встроен в генератор страниц, оптимизированных для СЕО, что позволяет увеличить доступность, не дублируя страницы! За всеми этими новшествами, наша цель осталась  прежней: помочь Вам повысить уровень конверсии и в разы вырастить Ваши продажи !Вы поймете, что новая версия 4.11 Advanced Search дает ощутимыерезультаты!]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[search_filter]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.12.7]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.1.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[199.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[224.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[179.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Oфициальный cоздатель модулей"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/766622-pprod/advanced-search-4.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/766622-pbig/advanced-search-4.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[2792]]></id><name><![CDATA[dmuassocprodcat]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[DMU Association flash Products / Categories]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Быстрое & массовое редактирование]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[An essential module for your products! You have over than 100 products? You want to control the association of your products to your categories? This module is for you!]]></description><author><![CDATA[Dream Me Up]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/mass-updates/2792-dmu-association-flash-products-categories.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/2792.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[An essential module for your products! You have over than 100 products? You want to control the association of your products to your categories? This module is for you!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Save time! In one interface, all in ajax (without reloading the page), see the products associated to a category. Look for products that you want to add to this category and add them in one click! You also can control the default category of your products directly through the icon on the right.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[quick_bulk_update]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.0.5]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[59.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Oфициальный cоздатель модулей"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/741974-pprod/dmu-association-flash-products-categories.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/741974-pbig/dmu-association-flash-products-categories.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[2937]]></id><name><![CDATA[bridgeconnector]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[STORE MANAGER]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Соединение с внешней программой (CRM, ERP...)]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[30-ДНЕВНАЯ БЕСПЛАТНАЯ ВЕРСИЯ! Решение для владельцев онлайн магазина которое Вы должны попробовать!&nbsp;&nbsp;*ПОБЕДИТЕЛЬ В НОМИНАЦИИ &#39;ЛУЧШИЙ МОДУЛЬ&#39; ЦЕРЕМОНИИ PRESTASHOP AWARDS*]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/third-party-data-integrations-crm-erp/2937-store-manager.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/2937.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[30-ДНЕВНАЯ БЕСПЛАТНАЯ ВЕРСИЯ! Решение для владельцев онлайн магазина которое Вы должны попробовать!&nbsp;&nbsp;*ПОБЕДИТЕЛЬ В НОМИНАЦИИ &#39;ЛУЧШИЙ МОДУЛЬ&#39; ЦЕРЕМОНИИ PRESTASHOP AWARDS*]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Экономьте время, деньги и ресурсы, позвольте Store Manager&rsquo;у делать рутинную работу вместо Вас. Store Manager поможет Вашему магазину выделиться из толпы!  Потратьте час, сэкономьте день! Store Manager for PrestaShop был создан &nbsp;чтобы работать на Вас. Это Ваш персональный ассистент который выполняет большинство рутинных задач экономя Вам время для более приятных дел. Импорт и экспорт, отчеты, дополнения - не нужно тратить дни разбираясь в деталях работы магазна, потратьте несколько часов чтобы научиться работать со Store Manager&rsquo;ом.  Приобретайте один Store Manager for PrestaShop вместо целой кучи модулей. Используйте один продукт для управления несколькими магазинами. Store Manager не требует особых навыков и знаний, Вам не нужно платить кому-то для поддержания вашего магазина в актуальном стостоянии. Большинство важных операций можно выполнить быстро и смостоятельно. &nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[export]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.0.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.1.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[299.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[339.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[269.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/572842-pprod/store-manager.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/572842-pbig/store-manager.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[4414]]></id><name><![CDATA[allinone_rewards]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[All-in-one Rewards: loyalty sponsorship affiliation...]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Обеспечения лояльности покупателей и акций "Приведи друга"]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Allows your customers to earn rewards, all grouped into a single account, while developing SEO and reputation of your shop: loyalty program, sponsorship (multilevel, self-promotional), affiliation, fa]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/referral-loyalty-programs/4414-all-in-one-rewards-loyalty-sponsorship-affiliation.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/4414.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Allows your customers to earn rewards, all grouped into a single account, while developing SEO and reputation of your shop: loyalty program, sponsorship (multilevel, self-promotional), affiliation, facebook and more. Your sales will really increase !]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Get tons of new customers and increase your brand reputation thanks to the All-in-one Rewards module !&nbsp;This module allows to set up a complete system of rewards in your shop to increase SEO and reputation thanks to the virality of the system, and to follow very precisely the performance.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[advertising_marketing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.1.5]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[199.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[224.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[179.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/617761-pprod/all-in-one-rewards-loyalty-sponsorship-affiliation.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/617761-pbig/all-in-one-rewards-loyalty-sponsorship-affiliation.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[4731]]></id><name><![CDATA[prestablog]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Professional blog]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Блог, форумов и новостей]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Best trafic module award 2015 &amp; 2019. Easy to install and use]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/blog-forum-news/4731-professional-blog.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/4731.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Best trafic module award 2015 &amp; 2019. Easy to install and use. Fully compatible with every language and will fit perfectly in your template, whether or not multilingual and/or multishop!&nbsp;Optimized for a better SEO.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Get in touch with your customers through a blog has become increasingly common for companies who want to build customer loyalty.No need to install a second cms to get all the features you need, this blog is everything you need!&nbsp;Search Engine optimisation (SEO)&nbsp;SEO have been one of the most important part of our developpment on our blog module,&nbsp;It will be a perfect and infallible tool to increase your visibility on the web.&nbsp;Responsive Design&nbsp;Our webdesign team have developped a template who pefectly integrate in all type of template. Responsive or not.&nbsp;Fast support&nbsp;100% of our customers get an anwser within 1mn to 6 hours maximum (period days worked) to help you as quickly as possible to implement your project.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[content_management]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.1.5]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.6.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[69.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[79.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[64.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Best Module Traffic"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/awards-traffic.png]]></badge><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/730685-pprod/professional-blog.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/730685-pbig/professional-blog.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[4982]]></id><name><![CDATA[pm_seointernallinking]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[SEO Internal Linking]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Естественная поисковая оптимизация]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Improve your SEO through internal linking strategy]]></description><author><![CDATA[Presta-Module]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/seo-natural-search-engine-optimization/4982-seo-internal-linking.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/4982.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Improve your SEO through internal linking strategy]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Enhance your PrestaShop SEO  Internal linking is the creation of links between pages of your shop, using keywords you want to achieve a better place on Google.  To optimize the SEO of your website, it is essential to create an internal linking that will allow search engines to browse your shop in the most easy way as possible. The goal is to provide maximum informations with the least clicks deep.  SEO Internal Linking PrestaShop module optimizes the organization of navigation in your store, and plays an essential role in your SEO strategy.  Define the keywords on which you wish to be listed and their landing pages, and let the module create the links for you!  If you want to add automatic links in your categories descriptions, consider installing our PrestaShop module HTML On Descriptions.  Do we really need internal linking?  Internal linking strategy based on specific keywords is an optimization method that has proven its worth. Especially to enhance a content relevance.  Among the disadvantages, you should know that the installation of these links is long and tedious, and requires to follow SEO good practices, to not over-optimize (which would be detected by Google), and must be updated regularly to track changes in your catalog.  With this in mind, we have developed this module, allowing you to deploy thousands of cross links between your pages within minutes, while being sure to observe best practice guidelines of White Hat SEO.  It has been designed to support both SEO agencies and e-shop owners. SEO Internal Linking is really simple to manage.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[seo]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.2.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[149.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[169.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[134.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Oфициальный cоздатель модулей"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/573343-pprod/seo-internal-linking.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/573343-pbig/seo-internal-linking.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[5255]]></id><name><![CDATA[ordertaxprofitreport]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Sales Reports Pro]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Статистика и анализ]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Create professional sales, tax, profit and profit margin reports in HTML format or export as a CSV / Excel file]]></description><author><![CDATA[Business Tech]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/analytics-statistics/5255-sales-reports-pro.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/5255.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Create professional sales, tax, profit and profit margin reports in HTML format or export as a CSV / Excel file.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[*** WINNER OF THE 2015 PRESTASHOP AWARDS CEREMONY FOR THE BEST MODULE ***  Get perfect visibility on your shop's and products' profitability! The default PrestaShop installation does not provide a one-click tool that allows you to obtain important accounting and financial data: tax due, net sales volume after discounts and, most importantly, profit and profit margin. Not only will this report provide you with all this data, but it will even allow you to answer questions like "what percentage of total sales and / or profits does this specific brand, supplier or product category represent ?". This stylish and pleasant AJAX based module allows you to generate different types of preformed reports with all this information. They can be viewed on screen in HTML format or exported as a CSV file to manipulate in Excel and / or import into any other information or accounting system.  This module is developed and published by Business Tech, certified PrestaShop developer and winner of the 2011, 2014 and 2017 PrestaShop Awards for "Best module", with over 7 years of experience working with Google and Facebook. You are guaranteed to buy a robust, reliable and quality module. Furthermore, at Business Tech, we have a fast and efficient tech support : when you contact us, you are talking directly to the developers, so you are sure to be well informed ! ]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[analytics_stats]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.10.7]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[149.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[169.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[134.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Oфициальный cоздатель модулей"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/963264-pprod/sales-reports-pro.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/963264-pbig/sales-reports-pro.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[5711]]></id><name><![CDATA[zipcodezone]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Shipping fees based on zipcodes]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Стоимость доставки]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Apply different shipping fees based on postal codes of your customers]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/shipping-costs/5711-shipping-fees-based-on-zipcodes.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/5711.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Apply different shipping fees based on postal codes of your customers.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[With PrestaShop, it is possible to apply different shipping fees based on country or state. However, this does not necessarily represent the reality of carriers. Some will charge higher prices for mountainous or remote areas for example (departments or overseas territories). Improve your shop&#39;s shipping system&nbsp;with this module which will allow you to apply different shipping fees based on zip code of your client. Using the zone system of PrestaShop, you will be able to cut a country into as many parts as you want. By department, area or whatever you want. This has the advantage of adapting the way you want your areas.&nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[shipping_logistics]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.4.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.6.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[59.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/650424-pprod/shipping-fees-based-on-zipcodes.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/650424-pbig/shipping-fees-based-on-zipcodes.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[6059]]></id><name><![CDATA[cdiscount]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Cdiscount Marketplace]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Торговая площадка]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Sell your products on the Cdiscount marketplace: catalogue export, automatic updating of prices and stocks, retrieval and management of orders]]></description><author><![CDATA[Common-Services]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/marketplaces/6059-cdiscount-marketplace.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/6059.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Sell your products on the Cdiscount marketplace: catalogue export, automatic updating of prices and stocks, retrieval and management of orders. Beneficiate from 3-month subscription free when you register on Cdiscount !]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[C Le Marché is one of France’s leading marketplaces.  Boost your sales! Make the most of the traffic generated by Cdiscount to sell your products and enjoy the numerous advantages which make Cdiscount such a success: - payment in 4 instalments (fully supported by Cdiscount) - multiple delivery methods, etc.  Cdiscount takes care of everything! Place your products for sale on the marketplace and manage your orders while Cdiscount takes care of the rest: traffic, easy and secure payment, marketing, etc.  1 single back office! Thanks to the Cdiscount for PrestaShop module, you no longer need to manage several different back offices. In just a few clicks, connect your PrestaShop site to your Cdiscount store and post your products: - Product descriptions are exported directly to the Cdiscount marketplace, - Prices and inventories are automatically updated, - Your orders will be directly imported and integrated into your PrestaShop store.  Practical and easy configuration! Once you have configured your module, exports are automatic meaning you no longer have any data to handle.  A module developed by an e-merchant for e-merchants! The module’s design is based on the early experience of online retailers. It was created by an e-merchants for the benefit of fellow e-merchants and developed by a team of professional developers, resulting in maximum user friendliness and efficiency.  Free technical support! Your purchase is guaranteed by free technical support provided unconditionally until your products are placed online and your first orders are imported.   *This offer applies for merchants already registered on CleMarché Marketplace and cannot be used in combination with any other ongoing Cdiscount.com offer.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[market_place]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.0.155]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.6.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[149.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[169.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[134.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/715585-pprod/cdiscount-marketplace.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/715585-pbig/cdiscount-marketplace.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[6144]]></id><name><![CDATA[gsnippetsreviews]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Customer Ratings and Reviews Pro + Google Rich Snippets]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Естественная поисковая оптимизация]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Conversion rate increase guaranteed: The&nbsp;most complete&nbsp;and powerful product rating &amp; review system, plus Google Rich Snippets functionality]]></description><author><![CDATA[Business Tech]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/seo-natural-search-engine-optimization/6144-customer-ratings-and-reviews-pro-google-rich-snippets.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/6144.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Conversion rate increase guaranteed: The&nbsp;most complete&nbsp;and powerful product rating &amp; review system, plus Google Rich Snippets functionality.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Get the best customer rating and review module for PrestaShop, and increase your conversion rate significantly! Moreover, with Google Rich Snippets, benefit from visually enhanced results on Google&#39;s search engine and increase your click rate, number of visitors and sales!&nbsp;If you have already purchased our&nbsp;&quot;Wall Posts&quot;&nbsp;module (sold separately on https://addons.prestashop.com/en/products-on-facebook-social-networks/4429-wall-posts.html), you can have any rating / review automatically posted on your Facebook page. The mechanism also integrates very well with the moderation tool, so that if moderation is enabled on the module, reviews will only be posted to Facebook once validated.&nbsp;This module is also fully compatible and integrates with Presta-Module&#39;s&nbsp;&quot;Advanced Pack 5&quot;&nbsp;module, available on https://addons.prestashop.com/en/cross-selling-product-bundles/1015-advanced-pack-5-create-bundles-of-products.html&nbsp;For shops whose&nbsp;head office is located in France,&nbsp;the module is compliant with the decree No. 2017-1436 of 29 September 2017 on &quot;information obligations relating to online consumer notices&quot; and in effect from 1 January 2018. For more information on the decree, visit : &nbsp;https://www.legifrance.gouv.fr/eli/decret/2017/9/29/ECOC1716649D/jo/texte&nbsp;&nbsp;This module is developed by BusinessTech, certified PrestaShop developer, with over 8 years of experience working with Google and Facebook and 4 times winner of PrestaShop Awards. You are guaranteed to buy a robust, reliable and quality module.&nbsp;Furthermore, at BusinessTech, we have a fast and efficient tech support : when you contact us, you are talking directly to the developers, so you are sure to be well informed !&nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[seo]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.4.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[99.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[114.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[89.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge><badge label="Oфициальный cоздатель модулей"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/963262-pprod/customer-ratings-and-reviews-pro-google-rich-snippets.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/963262-pbig/customer-ratings-and-reviews-pro-google-rich-snippets.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[6291]]></id><name><![CDATA[siretcustomergroup]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[SIRET and customer group]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Управления учетными записями клиентов]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Differentiate your business customers of individuals with this SIRET module which transfers the professionals in a given customer group]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/customer-administration/6291-siret-and-customer-group.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/6291.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Differentiate your business customers of individuals with this SIRET module which transfers the professionals in a given customer group.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Finally, you can easily manage your professional customers just by asking their SIRET to transfer them in a client group or there is no tax for example, with prices reduced (e.g. wholesalers)...]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.7.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[59.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/101289-pprod/siret-and-customer-group.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/101289-pbig/siret-and-customer-group.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[6337]]></id><name><![CDATA[codfee]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Cash On Delivery With Fee/Surcharge Plus (COD)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Оплата при доставке]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Charge a commission/fee to your customer when they choose cash on delivery/collect on delivery/pay on shipment! The most downloaded payment method]]></description><author><![CDATA[Idnovate]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/collect-on-delivery-cod/6337-cash-on-delivery-with-fee-surcharge-plus-cod.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/6337.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Charge a commission/fee to your customer when they choose cash on delivery/collect on delivery/pay on shipment! The most downloaded payment method. More than 5,000 downloads and highly rated!The favourite payment method for your customers!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Encourage sales with an optimized payment solution! Offer your customers the option to pay for their order when it is received. With this module, you can improve customer satisfaction by letting them have their orders before paying. A perfect solution for customers who are hesitant about certain purchases. ESSENTIAL MODULE! This module will increase your sales! You can offset the extra cost of this shipping method by charging a fee to the customer. The cash on delivery payment method allows your customers to pay for the order at the time of receiving their order, they pay on shipment. This payment method is the perfect solution for customers who do not trust other payment methods, such as a card payment or PayPal, and prefer to pay upon receiving their order. With this method, you can offset the additional cost normally associated with "cash on delivery" by charging a fee to customers that choose this payment method. This module allows you to add the "cash on delivery" payment method with the option of applying an extra fee. Compatible with back office orders! Also, you can configure as a pay upon cash on pickup! Customers will benefit from the payment options most used and preferred by them. This module DOES NOT require a monthly fee or any other fee, you buy it once and you use it without any restrictions.&nbsp;Our guarantees&nbsp;✪&nbsp;We are&nbsp;a PrestaShop Partner agency. All our developers are certified by PrestaShop.✔&nbsp;We can customize the module or make any modifications that you may need. Contact us for a quote. Do you have any questions or concerns? Send us a message! We will happily answer any questions]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[payments_gateways]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.3.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.6.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[44.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[39.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Oфициальный cоздатель модулей"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/812425-pprod/cash-on-delivery-with-fee-surcharge-plus-cod.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/812425-pbig/cash-on-delivery-with-fee-surcharge-plus-cod.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[6344]]></id><name><![CDATA[swissrounded]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Rounded to 5ct for Switzerland]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Управление ценами]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[This module enables the management of rounded to 5 cents on your shop. This module is recommended for e-Swiss merchants using PrestaShop]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/pricing/6344-rounded-to-5ct-for-switzerland.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/6344.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[This module enables the management of rounded to 5 cents on your shop. This module is recommended for e-Swiss merchants using PrestaShop.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Show prices that are always rounded up to five cents, to avoid confusion when your customers navigate your store.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[17.1.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[89.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[104.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[84.99]]></GBP></price><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/882910-pprod/rounded-to-5ct-for-switzerland.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/882910-pbig/rounded-to-5ct-for-switzerland.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[6356]]></id><name><![CDATA[pm_multiplefeatures]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Multiple Features - Assign your features as you want]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Поиск и фильтры]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Multiple Features allows you to assign multiple values ​​of features to your products]]></description><author><![CDATA[Presta-Module]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/search-filters/6356-multiple-features-assign-your-features-as-you-want.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/6356.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Multiple Features allows you to assign multiple values ​​of features to your products]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Add features to your PrestaShop catalog without limits!  With Multiple Features, you can assign as many values as necessary for the same product and the same feature. Remove this PrestaShop limitation and start using your features as you want!  If you also use our layered navigation system Advanced Search 4 (Winner of PrestaShop Best Module Awards 2012), you can give to your customers a more relevant research in your catalog.  Customer study :  Ocarat.com: "Some jewelry may have a different composition and an alloy of several metals. PrestaShop provides the ability to associate a feature to a product. However, I want to integrate in my shop a gold ring set with diamonds and emeralds. But features tab does not allow me to do so. I can't assign multiple values to a single purpose. So I have to choose between gold, diamonds or emeralds. Multiple Features remove PrestaShop limits and allows you to use features as you want !"]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[search_filter]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.4.6]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[44.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[39.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Oфициальный cоздатель модулей"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/573403-pprod/multiple-features-assign-your-features-as-you-want.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/573403-pbig/multiple-features-assign-your-features-as-you-want.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[6946]]></id><name><![CDATA[invoicepayment]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Invoice Payment ]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Оплата счетом-фактурой]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[The payment by invoice is very popular in many countries, especially among German and Swiss customersWith this module, you can offer the invoice payment method to your registered customers in order to]]></description><author><![CDATA[Silbersaiten]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/payment-invoice/6946-invoice-payment.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/6946.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[The payment by invoice is very popular in many countries, especially among German and Swiss customersWith this module, you can offer the invoice payment method to your registered customers in order to provide a safe shopping experience.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[With this module, you can offer a bill payment to your users. You can define from what order this payment method is available for your customers.&nbsp;For example, for your regular customers this method should be available from their 2nd order. You also can define the order amount limit this method is available to.&nbsp;Further, you can set the payment terms, that depend on the selected order status. After the status has changed, the payment term also appears in the PDF invoice.&nbsp;In the module&#39;s configuration you also have a text area for further information. For example, you can specify where the customer should transfer the money to. This information appears in the PDF invoice]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[payments_gateways]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.0.6]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[44.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[39.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Oфициальный cоздатель модулей"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/689390-pprod/invoice-payment.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/689390-pbig/invoice-payment.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[7422]]></id><name><![CDATA[groupinc]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Price Increment/Reduction by group, category and more]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Акции и Подарки]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Set the product prices which do you want to really show. Make increments, reductions (discounts) and fixed prices with an unlimited conditions and combinations]]></description><author><![CDATA[Idnovate]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/promotions-gifts/7422-price-increment-reduction-by-group-category-and-more.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/7422.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Set the product prices which do you want to really show. Make increments, reductions (discounts) and fixed prices with an unlimited conditions and combinations.&nbsp;You can modify your product prices, massively or individually, as you prefer.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Change the product prices massivelyYou can change the price of the products massively, setting an increment, a discount or a fixed price using these conditions:- Category- Product- Customer group- Customer- Country- Zone- Supplier- Manufacturer- Language- Currency&nbsp;If you choose the percentage type, it can be calculated from Retail or Wholesale price and with or without taxes.To apply the rule, you have this additional controls:&nbsp;- Minimum threshold price- Maximum threshold price- Date From- Date To&nbsp;And also, you can control the final price result setting a minimum and a maximum price with:&nbsp;- Minimum result price- Maximum result price&nbsp;The module adds a priority system in case that two or more rules must be applied to the same product. In this case, you can establish a priority to set the order and if you want to only execute one of this rules (using the option:&quot;Apply only one condition&quot;).&nbsp;&nbsp;Discounts managementTo apply and manage the discounts with our module, you have 3 options:&nbsp;- Show reduction as discount: With this option enabled, the reduction is showed like discount (specific price), then the price of the product will show the old price and the new price with the discount amount/percentage.* Only works if the rule configuration create with our module is a discount.&nbsp;- Skip other discounts: If the product has a previous discount, the rule will not be applied to this product.- Override discounts: If the product has a previous discount, the rule will be applied and the previous discount will be overrided (ommitted but not deleted).This 2 options, are applicable with any of the configurations that you can do with our module.&nbsp;Examples of using the module:- Very useful for the promotions season like Black Friday, Sales, Christmas, Cyber Monday, etc... to change the prices in the products with begin and end date activating and deactivating the offer automatically.- You can set an increment in the catalog products only or a currency (or currencies) to avoid the currency conversion losses.- Set a reduction for a VIP customers group offering them more competitives prices or set an increment to your Resellers group to get more benefits from the products.- Change the prices in a Country or Zone and promote the sales in this geographical area.&nbsp;* The module doesn&#39;t change the original price of the product (you never will lose the original price).&nbsp;★ &iexcl;New! ★ -&gt; Attributes filter (combinations)With the new attributes filter you can set the price changes only for an specific product combination.Example: Modify the price only of your product with the L and XL size and not for the prices of the S and M size.&nbsp;★ &iexcl;New! ★ -&gt; Features filterWith the new features filter you can set the price changes only for products with an specific feature.Example: Modify the price only for the cotton and synthetic products.&nbsp;★ &iexcl;New! ★ -&gt; Quantity product units filterAdded a new field to set the m&iacute;nimum quantity units of the product that must be in the cart to apply the change in the price.Example: Modify the price of product from 3 units, then, the price of product will be changed automatically only if 3 or more products are added to the cart.&nbsp;★ &iexcl;New! ★ -&gt; Change the prices within a period (date from and date to)Configure the price changes (increment, discount or fixed price) between 2 dates, or from a date or until a date. It&#39;s an optional field, is not necessary to set a date, if 0 there&#39;s no period limit to apply the rule.Example: Apply the modification (increment, discount or fixed price) from 2016-10-20 until 2016-10-30Example: Apply the modification (increment, discount or fixed price) from 2016-10-20.Example: Apply the modification (increment, discount or fixed price) until 2016-10-30.&nbsp;&nbsp;★ &iexcl;New! ★ -&gt; Threshold prices to apply the rulesApply the change in your prices only for the product which price is between a threshold.Example: Apply the modification (increment, discount or fixed price) in the price of products which cost is more than 10&euro; and less than 30&euro;.Example: Apply the modification (increment, discount or fixed price) in the price of products which cost is more than 50&euro;.Example: Apply the modification (increment, discount or fixed price) in the price of products which cost is less than 100&euro;.&nbsp;&nbsp;★ &iexcl;New! ★ -&gt; Minimum and maximum result priceNow, you can set a minimum and a maximum price to get if the result of the increment or discount is below or above this prices.Example: Minimum result price = 100 and Maximum result price 200If the result price after the rule application is below 100&euro; (89&euro; for example), the product price will be 100&euro;. If the result price after the rule application is above 200&euro; (205&euro; for example) the product price will be 200&euro;.Example: Minimum result price = 100 and Maximum result price 0If the result price after the rule application is below 100&euro; (89&euro; for example), the product price will be 100&euro;. If the result price after the rule application is 105&euro; the product price will be 105&euro;.Example: Minimum result price = 0 and Maximum result price 100If the result price after the rule application is above 100&euro; (105&euro; for example) the product price will be 100&euro;. If the result price after the rule application is 80&euro; the product price will be 80&euro;.&nbsp;&nbsp;★ &iexcl;New! ★ -&gt; Category tree to select the categoriesNew friendly interface in the Categories selector. Now, the display is in a category tree to select the categories easily.&nbsp;&nbsp;★ &iexcl;New! ★ -&gt; Friendly multiple selectors interfaceNew friendly multiple selector interface with add and remove buttons and a search box.&nbsp;&nbsp;Geolocation compatibilityFull compatibility with Prestashop Geolocation to change the prices by Zone and Country. If the customer is not logged and the Prestashop Geolocation is enabled, the prices will be shown by the geolocation IP Country of the customer.If logged, the country and the zone calculation is done from the address delivery.&nbsp;&nbsp;Apply a markup or offer a discount in your productsFeel free to play with a markup in the price of your products creating an increment or a reduction configuration by category, by product, by customer group, by customer, by country, by zone, by supplier and by manufacturer.&nbsp;Example: You can create a new category, associate the products to this category and with our module you could set all this category products to 20$ without changing the original product price and without creating complicated discount rules to obtain the desired price.&nbsp;&nbsp;No multistore needed for the same catalog productsThe customers group filter allows to avoid creating a multistore for a B2B and B2C store, sharing the same catalog products but with different prices in each.&nbsp;&nbsp;Our guarantees&nbsp;✪ We are a PrestaShop Partner agency. All our developers are certified by PrestaShop.✔ We can customize the module or make any modifications that you may need. Contact us for a quote.&nbsp;Do you have any questions or concerns? Send us a message! We will happily answer any questions&nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[pricing_promotion]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.4.9]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.6.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[59.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge><badge label="Oфициальный cоздатель модулей"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/812413-pprod/price-increment-reduction-by-group-category-and-more.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/812413-pbig/price-increment-reduction-by-group-category-and-more.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[7484]]></id><name><![CDATA[newsletterpro]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Newsletter Pro]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Рассылка новостей и SMS]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[This module for PrestaShop allows you to create and send your own newsletters with different products from your store using many customizable templates]]></description><author><![CDATA[ProQuality]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/newsletter-sms/7484-newsletter-pro.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/7484.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[This module for PrestaShop allows you to create and send your own newsletters with different products from your store using many customizable templates.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[We all know that advertising plays a key role in promoting any business. Using our newsletter will boost your sales faster and easier than any other newsletter module available on the market. This module is an easy and fast way to send customizable newsletters about top selling products or special offers to your clients.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[emailing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.8.6]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.17]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[79.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[89.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[74.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Oфициальный cоздатель модулей"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/724699-pprod/newsletter-pro.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/724699-pbig/newsletter-pro.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[7507]]></id><name><![CDATA[lgsitemaps]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Multilingual and Multistore Sitemap Pro – SEO]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Естественная поисковая оптимизация]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Generate sitemaps of all the urls of your store automatically (cron), in all the languages of your store (multilingual), for all your stores (multistore) and including product, categories and manufact]]></description><author><![CDATA[Línea Gráfica]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/seo-natural-search-engine-optimization/7507-multilingual-and-multistore-sitemap-pro-seo.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/7507.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Generate sitemaps of all the urls of your store automatically (cron), in all the languages of your store (multilingual), for all your stores (multistore) and including product, categories and manufacturer images.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Improve your shop SEO by generating a Sitemaps! Index your shop urls in the search engine (Google, Bing, Ask) quick and easily. With our module, you can automate the generation and configuration of your Sitemaps, so you do not have to worry about.  4 types of sitemapsOur module is fully-automatic and allows you to create 4 types of sitemaps:one sitemap that includes all the URLs of your Product pagesone sitemap that includes all the URLs of your Category pagesone sitemap that includes all the URLs of your CMS pagesone sitemap that includes all the URLs of your Manufacturer pages Really easy to configure sitemapsConfigure each type of sitemap separately.Choose the type (product, category, CMS or manufacturer)Choose the store (multistore)Choose the priority of indexation of the urls of the sitemap from 0.1 to 1.0 compared to the urls of your other sitemaps ("priority" tag)Indicate how frequently (daily, weekly, monthly, yearly) the pages contained into the sitemap are supposed to be modified ("changefreq" tag)Choose to include or not the urls of your product, categories and manufacturers images into the sitemapChoose to automatically inform or not the search engines Google, Bing and Ask about the sitemap creation (ping request) Really easy to generate the sitemapsClick on the button "Generate" and the sitemaps are generated automatically without overloading the server and without timeout problem. Perfect for large, medium and small catalogues of products. Multistore sitemapsThis module is compatible with PrestaShop monostore and multistore system. It automatically detects all your stores and allows you to easily generate sitemaps for all of them.Please note that the module generate different sitemaps by store, each store has its 4 own sitemaps (Products, Categories, CMS and Manufacturers). Multilingual sitemapsOur module allows you to create sitemaps in all the languages of your store so that you can easily improve the SEO of your store in several languages.For each type of sitemap (products, categories, CMS and manufacturers), the module generates one sitemap that includes the URLS in all languages, as recommended by Google.Our sitemaps are based on Google official guidelines so that you get the best SEO results. Image indexationAnother feature of our module is the possibility to include product, categories and manufacturers images into the sitemaps so that Google can index them. It makes your store visible and accessible from Google Image Search, which automatically increases the visibility of your store. Sitemap indexThe module automatically creates a sitemap index to make it easier the management of your sitemaps, as recommended by Google. The index contains all the urls of your sitemaps, you just need to enter the url of the sitemap index into Google Webmaster Tools to submit all your sitemaps at once. Automatic split up of large sitemapsOur module can create sitemaps for all sizes of catalogues. Google only accepts sitemaps that weights up to 10MB or 50,000 urls, this is why our module automatically split up the large sitemaps into several files so that you don't have any problems in Google. Automatic creation via the CronYou will find inside the module a Cron URL that allows you to generate all your sitemaps automatically and on a regular basis without having to do anything. You just need to copy and paste this url into a Cron module or into your hosting panel to execute these tasks automatically and on a regular basis. ]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[seo]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.5.11]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.17]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.6.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[69.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[79.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[64.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge><badge label="Oфициальный cоздатель модулей"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/1001242-pprod/multilingual-and-multistore-sitemap-pro-seo.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/1001242-pbig/multilingual-and-multistore-sitemap-pro-seo.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[8022]]></id><name><![CDATA[resumeniva]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Tax Summary]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Бухгалтерии и выставления счетов]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Module for Prestashop store that helps us to make easier and faster the tax summary]]></description><author><![CDATA[Deindo Ideas]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/accounting-invoicing/8022-tax-summary.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/8022.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Module for Prestashop store that helps us to make easier and faster the tax summary.&nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[With this module you’ll have your company’s accounting up to date, especially when you have to deliver your tax summary. This program allows us to choose the option of filter the information by several ways: type of tax, pay method and order condition. Only choosing two dates, you’ll get the list of the taxes charged on orders. This doesn’t change although the orders are billed or not billed. The module also includes an option to enter some information about customers (Full name and ID), and then, filter the summary by this value.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[billing_invoicing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.2.8]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[44.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[39.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Oфициальный cоздатель модулей"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/704092-pprod/tax-summary.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/704092-pbig/tax-summary.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[8057]]></id><name><![CDATA[marketplace]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Advanced Multi Vendor Marketplace]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Создания торговой площадки]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Turn your Prestashop store into a marketplace where sellers can add products, manage orders, manage profile, shop, product name and descriptions in multi-language]]></description><author><![CDATA[Webkul]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/marketplace-creation/8057-advanced-multi-vendor-marketplace.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/8057.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Turn your Prestashop store into a marketplace where sellers can add products, manage orders, manage profile, shop, product name and descriptions in multi-language. Seller can have complete SEO friendly shop and profile page.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Module is GDPR Compliant Add terms and conditions in seller registration form. Set whether to show the admin commission to seller or not.Admin can customize the display of seller details.Enable/disable the multi-language functionality.Choose whether seller can activate/deactivate their products or not.Choose whether sellers can activate/deactivate their shop or not.Admin can view the earnings of payment accepted orders or of confirmed orders on transaction page.Allow/Disallow custom CSS for MarketplaceDisplay “Become a Seller” option on navigation bar, footer bar, and bottom info bar at the front end.Enable/Disable automatic approval of seller’s request.Enable/Disable automatic approval of seller’s products.Admin can allow/disallow sellers to provide their social profile links.Admin can allow/disallow sellers to apply pre-added tax rules on their products.Allow sellers to add meta description & title to their products.Sellers can now set the visibility of their products, if allowed by admin.Sellers can select the availability preferences for their out-of-stock products.Sellers can add EAN-13, UPC barcode, ISBN, and reference code to their products.Allow/disallow sellers to "Create Combination" for their products using admin added attributes & values.Allow/disallow sellers to "Add Features" for their products using admin added features & values.Allow/Disallow sellers to apply admin added shipping methods to their products.If enabled, then products need to be approved manually after it has been updated by seller.Admin can assign theexisting admin products to the sellers.Admin can add payment modes through which it can transfer the seller’s amount.Rollback seller transaction data if admin/seller changes the status of an order to canceled.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[5.2.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.6.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[199.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[224.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[179.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Oфициальный cоздатель модулей"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/1290384-pprod/advanced-multi-vendor-marketplace.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/1290384-pbig/advanced-multi-vendor-marketplace.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[8204]]></id><name><![CDATA[facebookpsconnect]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Social Login]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Логин / Подключение]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Let your customers easily register and log in to your shop in 1 click via Facebook, Paypal, Amazon, Google or Twitter]]></description><author><![CDATA[Business Tech]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/social-login-connect/8204-social-login.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/8204.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Let your customers easily register and log in to your shop in 1 click via Facebook, Paypal, Amazon, Google or Twitter.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Did you know that one of the main purchase obstacles on the Internet is to have to create a custom account?&nbsp;With "Social Login" module, boost your conversion rate by letting your customers easily register and log in to your shop through their favorite social network: Facebook, Paypal, Amazon, Google or Twitter.&nbsp;&nbsp;REDUCE YOUR ABANDONED CART RATE !&nbsp;This is a known fact in the world of e-commerce that&nbsp;the less friction there is during checkout, the higher the chance is that the customer will finalize his or her order, considerably reducing cart abandonment.&nbsp;Social networks use has largely expanded and is experiencing unprecedented growth. Today there are&nbsp;more than 3 billion active social network users worldwide.&nbsp;Use this astounding craze to your advantage!&nbsp;Thanks to the "Social Login" module, your customers will be able to register and log in to your shop&nbsp;in only 1 click.They'll just have to connect to their favorite social network, as Facebook, Paypal, Amazon, Google or Twitter. This will make&nbsp;the ordering process much quicker and easier.&nbsp;Moreover, with PayPal, it's a real 1 click registration because PayPal also automatically fills the customer's shipping/billing address in the customer's account.&nbsp;But it's not all! If you have a 1.7 PrestaShop version, you can go even further&nbsp;linking this module with the Presta-Module's "One Click Order" one (available separately here: https://addons.prestashop.com/en/express-checkout-process/29273-one-click-order.html) and offering to your customers&nbsp;not only&nbsp;to log in 1 click but also&nbsp;to order in 1 click!&nbsp;Placing an order on your site has never been easier!&nbsp;&nbsp;[NEW] TAKE ADVANTAGE OF TOTAL FREEDOM IN POSITIONING YOUR CONNECTORS&nbsp;The module offers you multiple possibilities to position your connectors and even goes so far as to leave your hand completely to precisely place your connection buttons. In fact, in addition to the standard positions (see "Features" section of this product file), such as the user block, the login page or the order funnel (for 1.7 PrestaShop versions), the module offers you two advanced position tools:&nbsp;- HTML elements use:&nbsp;select the HTML element on which you want to see the buttons, fill it in the back office and the module takes care of everything!- Shortcode use:&nbsp;for pro, only fill out a configuration form and get the shortcode to insert directly in your theme template.&nbsp;&nbsp;[NEW] ENDLESSLY CUSTOMIZE QUICK CONNECTION BLOCKS&nbsp;Whether you choose a classic or an advanced position for your connectors, the module offers you&nbsp;a complete CSS tool&nbsp;that allows you to&nbsp;fully customize&nbsp;the appearance of the connection block. Take advantage of this advanced feature to make your shop visually unique!&nbsp;&nbsp;THE PRESTASHOP SOCIAL LOGIN MODULE THE MOST ROBUST AND GRAPHICALLY CAREFUL&nbsp;This state-of-the-art "Social Login" module was implemented&nbsp;with the latest standards&nbsp;of Facebook, PayPal, Amazon, Google and Twitter, insuring&nbsp;a high level of quality and robustness.&nbsp;We have completely rebuilt the interface of the module to make its configuration&nbsp;as pleasant and intuitive as possible.&nbsp;Finally, we have also&nbsp;reworked the design of the connection buttons&nbsp;to allow you to opt for a style of buttons much more modern than before. You have the opportunity to give a resolutely current style to your shop.&nbsp;&nbsp;ATTRACT NEW CUSTOMERS BY OFFERING THEM A DISCOUNT IN EXCHANGE FOR A CONNECTION THROUGH A SOCIAL NETWORK&nbsp;You want to attract new customers? What better than to offer a voucher in exchange for a quick connection through their favorite social network?&nbsp;They will not only waste time filling out a registration form&nbsp;but in addition they will&nbsp;take advantage of a voucher.&nbsp;Ordering will be greatly facilitated!&nbsp;The module gives you the possibility&nbsp;to highlight, or not,&nbsp;this offer in different positions on your website and to fully configure its application conditions&nbsp;directly from the module's back office.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[social_networks]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.0.13]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[69.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[79.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[64.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Oфициальный cоздатель модулей"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/963266-pprod/social-login.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/963266-pbig/social-login.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[8296]]></id><name><![CDATA[idxcookies]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[GDPR Cookies Law (Advice - Audit - Blocking)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Администрация]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Complies with the European Cookies Law (included in GDPR). Displays an advice with information about the Cookies used in your shop and allows the customer to block cookies that do not interest them]]></description><author><![CDATA[InnovaDeluxe]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/legal/8296-gdpr-cookies-law-advice-audit-blocking.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/8296.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Complies with the European Cookies Law (included in GDPR). Displays an advice with information about the Cookies used in your shop and allows the customer to block cookies that do not interest them. Includes powerful store cookie auditing system.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[We will help your customers to accept cookies policy of your store to obey with the law on data collection. This module runs in your online store when your cookies legal texts, are clearly specifying what type of cookies are you using and what is the data collecting destination.To determine the type of cookies you are using, please ask an expert to check your Prestashop store. To learn how to prepare the legal text you need to include in your store, you can ask a GDPR and LSSI experienced adviser or check this guide provided by the Official Data Protection Agency. The module includes a powerful auditing system, to check which cookies are generating internally the modules you have installed. The module will review each section of the front office of your store and will list all the cookies detected, which you can categorize to show the information of each one in the cookie advice. At this time, you cannot audit cookies from external domains, but you can add them manually. You can use any extension for your browser and then add them manually to the module. A new and much more powerful cookie warning has been created, in which you can display the information of the cookies distributed by the type of cookies. For example separated by Essential Cookies, Performance Cookies, Analytical Cookies, Third Party Cookies, etc... With information specific to each type of cookie and each cookie. The visitor can configure the cookies that your store uses on his browser to suit his or her needs, and can block cookies that do not interest him or her, such as those from third parties or analytics. Cookies that are essential for the proper functioning of the shop cannot be deactivated. You will be able to decide which cookies are essential. Remember that as important as having this module is to have some legal texts concerning the collection of data through correct Cookies Multi-Store UsageThis module is compatible with multi-store Prestashop module. You can install the module in all your stores in a multi-store and use different configurations for each of them or configure once for all stores.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.1.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.6.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[59.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Oфициальный cоздатель модулей"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/671904-pprod/gdpr-cookies-law-advice-audit-blocking.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/671904-pbig/gdpr-cookies-law-advice-audit-blocking.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[8734]]></id><name><![CDATA[lgcookieslaw]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[EU Cookie Law Complies GDPR (Banner + Cookie Blocker)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Администрация]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[This module allows you to fully comply with the GDPR/LOPD Cookies Section ]]></description><author><![CDATA[Línea Gráfica]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/legal/8734-eu-cookie-law-complies-gdpr-banner-cookie-blocker.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/8734.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[This module allows you to fully comply with the GDPR/LOPD Cookies Section . Display a responsive and custom warning banner and disable cookies when users enter your website until you obtain their consent.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Our module allows you to fully complies with the European Cookie Law / PECR.Updated to comply with the latest GDPR modifications of Cookies. Complete compliance with the GDPR Besides displaying a warning banner, our module is the only one that allows you to block the cookies when users enter your store. As established by the law, you "shall ensure that the storing of information, or the gaining of access to information already stored, in the terminal equipment of a subscriber or user is only allowed on condition that the subscriber or user concerned has given his or her consent, having been provided with clear and comprehensive information." Please note that all the other cookie modules sold on Addons only allows you to display a warning banner regardless of the user consent. Cookies are installed on the users' computer without obtaining their consent and regardless of their will. It also gives you the option to customize the module to meet 100% with the new requirements of the RGPD (European Union). Our Cookies module complies with the Right of rectification, with it users can delete the cookies installed from the site simply by accessing a URL or even from their own customer profile. Main features of the modulesDisplay a warning banner on every page to inform users about the use of cookies and ask for their consentDisable a list of modules when users enter the website because warning users about cookies is useless and illegal if you have already installed cookies on their computer.Enable these cookies after having obtained their consent or maintain them disabled if they refuse.Fully customize the warning banner (color, text, link, font, position, multilingual mode, transparency, buttons...) Getting the user consent The module includes 2 different ways to ask user consent, you can choose between:Acceptance through a button: Users must click on the "I accept" button in the warning banner to give his consent. As soon as users give their consent, the warning banner disappears and all the modules using cookies will get enabled and will work as usual. But if users refuse to give their consent, the disabled modules will remain disabled. We recommend you to use this mode, this one allows you to fully comply with the law.Acceptance through the navigation: (If you choose this option you should know that it does not comply with the new update of the GDPR) If users continue browsing the website, they will accept the use of cookies. The warning banner is displayed on the first page on which users arrive with a message like « By continuing browsing the website, you accept the use of cookies ». As soon as users decide to go to another page, the banner automatically disappears and the disabled modules will get enabled. Note: the consent remains valid during the period of time set in the module interface (we recommend you not to go over 13 months) IMPORTANT: Línea Gráfica will in no case be liable for any damages or losses that may be caused by activating options that do not comply with the RGPD. Customizing the banner content and design As recommended by the European authority, the module allows you to customize the warning message inside the banner (to inform users about the cookies users and their purpose) and add a "More information" button into the banner that take users to a CMS page of your store (to explain in details the use of cookies on your store). The warning banner is responsive and will always be displayed full-width. The module comes with a Wysiwyg editor that allows you to fully customize the content of the banner (font, color, effects, html code, links...). You can also choose from the configuration page the background color of the banner, its percentage of opacity (transparency) and its position (top or bottom of the page). Moreover, the module is multilingual and automatically detects all the languages of your store, which allows you to set a different warning message per language. Note: the module is designed to not display a warning message when search engines robots crawl you store in order not to affect your SEO. Disabling the modules that use cookies This is the only module that allows you to choose the modules/cookies that you want to disable until users give their consent. This feature is compulsory because it is useless and illegal to inform users if you have already installed cookies on their computer with their consent. "Member States shall ensure that the storing of information, or the gaining of access to information already stored, in the terminal equipment of a subscriber or user is only allowed on condition that the subscriber or user concerned has given his or her consent, having been provided with clear and comprehensive information, in accordance with Directive 95/46/EC” EU Cookie Law To comply with the directive of the EU Cookie Law, we recommend you to disable the tracking (Google Analytics), social sharing (Facebook " Like ", Google " +1 ", etc.) and targeted advertising modules. Please note that all modules that are required for the good running of your PrestaShop store (ex: basket cookie, session cookie...) don't require any consents. Multistore mode The module is compatible with multistore and allows you to display the same notification banner on each one of your shop but the consent is the same for all shops. If you accept the use of cookies on one of your shop, the module will consider that you accept the use of cookies for all your other shops (mention it on your cookie policy) and the notification banner will not be shown when you go to your other shops.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.4.20]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.6.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[29.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[34.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[27.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Oфициальный cоздатель модулей"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/1028451-pprod/eu-cookie-law-complies-gdpr-banner-cookie-blocker.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/1028451-pbig/eu-cookie-law-complies-gdpr-banner-cookie-blocker.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[8741]]></id><name><![CDATA[dmulistecommandes]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[DMU Improved Order List]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Управление заказами]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Save time on the processing of your orders! Avoid having to enter each order one after the other to get all the details. This module lets you know everything from your order list]]></description><author><![CDATA[Dream Me Up]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/order-management/8741-dmu-improved-order-list.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/8741.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Save time on the processing of your orders! Avoid having to enter each order one after the other to get all the details. This module lets you know everything from your order list.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[The more orders you have to process, the more this module will save you time. As much by the fact that all information is available from the order list and because you will be able to change status in mass with this module.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.2.5]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[59.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[69.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[54.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Oфициальный cоздатель модулей"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/740079-pprod/dmu-improved-order-list.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/740079-pbig/dmu-improved-order-list.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[8895]]></id><name><![CDATA[freedeliverymanager]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Free Delivery Manager]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Стоимость доставки]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[This is an ideal solution for increasing the amount of the average sales transaction]]></description><author><![CDATA[TimActive]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/shipping-costs/8895-free-delivery-manager.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/8895.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[This is an ideal solution for increasing the amount of the average sales transaction. According to the rules you have chosen, you encourage customers to increase the value of their purchases in order to take advantage of free delivery.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Developing your sales by increasing the value of transactions has never been an easy thing to implement. The &ldquo;Free Delivery Manager&rdquo; module is actually the perfect solution for offering your respected customers free shipping through objective rules. It is the promise of a rise in the amount of orders with total control of delivery costs.  The module allows you to calculate in advance, with the help of precise rules, the necessary conditions for unlocking free delivery. The management and monitoring are done according to carriers, delivery area, price, weight, or any other criteria you term as important for your business.  The &ldquo;Free Delivery Manager&rdquo; module offers control of delivery costs by releasing delivery available as a function of criteria you have chosen. All the carriers have their own price list. You may, for example, indicate a minimum order amount by carrier In presenting to the customer, in their order summary, the amount remaining before delivery is available, so you definitely encourage them to order more.  Highly detailed statistics visually present two types of reports together. The first one presents the number of orders that have benefited from free delivery, as well as the total and per-order amount that this cost you. You really control the impact of delivery costs. The second report displays the detail of costs caused by free postage and the orders where the rules for free shipping are applied. Thus, the &ldquo;Free Delivery Manager&rdquo; module increases the value of transactions as well as the number of orders!  This module has been constantly evolving, many thanks to user feedback. TimActive, in fact, grants great importance to your perception of our solutions and of the improvements that can be added.&nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[shipping_logistics]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.6.21]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.6.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[89.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[104.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[84.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge><badge label="Oфициальный cоздатель модулей"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/691962-pprod/free-delivery-manager.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/691962-pbig/free-delivery-manager.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[8934]]></id><name><![CDATA[migrationpro]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[инструмент обновления и переноса PrestaShop]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Миграции и сохранения данных]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Обновите Prestashop 1.4, 1.5 или 1.6 до Prestashop 1]]></description><author><![CDATA[MigrationPro]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/data-migration-backup/8934--prestashop.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/8934.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Обновите Prestashop 1.4, 1.5 или 1.6 до Prestashop 1.7 за мгновение! MigrationPro — это лучший модуль миграции из Prestashop в Prestashop, поможет перенести все ваши данные, а также всегда поддерживать свой магазин в полностью обновленном состоянии.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[У вас есть еще какие-либо вопросы о лучшем инструменте, который обновляет ваш PrestaShop до последней версии? Вы уже используете другой модуль, и миграция завершилась полным крахом? Пора исправить положение — получите отличные преимущества! Встречайте MigrationPro! MigrationPro — это лучший модуль миграции из Prestashop в PrestaShop, который позволяет быстро и эффективно перенести старый магазин Prestashop в последнюю версию приложения. По сравнению с нынешними конкурентами у MigrationPro есть много преимуществ для продавцов:перенос данных из старой версии вашего магазина PrestaShop в новую занимает всего одно мгновение;много БЕСПЛАТНЫХ дополнительных возможностей по сравнению с конкурентами, которые берут с вас ДЕНЬГИ;лучший имидж на рынке по отзывам и свидетельствам клиентов (поддержка клиентов — это главное). Переносятся следующие категории данных: 1. Товары и категории:Общая информация: имя, статус, описание, идентификатор товара, ссылочный номер и т.д.линейки и преимущества товаров;настройки доставки: ширина, высота, глубина, вес, дополнительные транспортные сборы, бесплатные носители; цены: цена (без налогов), цена (с налогом), цена за единицу (без налога), конкретные цены, настройки налогов и т.д.настройки оптимизации поисковых систем (SEO): мета-название, мета-описание, ключевые слова, обратные ссылки, взаимные ссылки, текст ссылки и т.д.кастомизация товара;изображения товаров и категорий: основные и уменьшенные изображения. 2. Заказы:общая информация: ссылочный номер заказа, идентификатор заказа, статус заказа, цены и т.д.;доставка;оплата;список товаров;счета-фактуры и условия доставки;комментарии пользователей, сообщения клиентов;статус заказа;корзины покупок;кредит 3. Клиенты и сотрудники:общая информация: имя, фамилия, адрес электронной почты, статус, профиль, язык и т.д..;можно сохранить пароли. 4. Скидки и купоны:правила корзины (скидочные коды);правила каталожных цен. 5. Налоги:налоги;группы налогов;налоговые правила для начисления налогов на товары 6. Условия доставки и перевозки:общие настройки: название перевозчика, время в пути, скорость, url отслеживания;места отправки и затраты; добавление статуса стоимости погрузки-разгрузки, статус бесплатной доставки, тип выставляемых счетов, налог на доставку, поведение вне диапазона, диапазоны цен (все зоны, все диапазоны);размер, вес и доступ к группе: максимальная ширина посылки (см), максимальная высота посылки (см), максимальная глубина посылки (см), максимальный вес посылки (кг). 7. Страницы системы управления отношениями с клиентами (CMS):общая информация: имя, статус, содержание, индексация, статуса перемещения;настройки оптимизации поисковых систем (SEO): мета-название, мета-описание, ключевые слова, обратные ссылки, взаимные ссылки, текст ссылки и т.д.категории CMS 8. Сообщения клиентов и услуги для клиентов:сообщения клиентов из контактной формы;услуги для клиентов;возвраты товара 9. Данные мульти-магазина:группы магазинов;магазины;все данные каждого магазина (товары, категория, клиенты, заказы и т.д.). 10. Данные локализации:языки;валюты;страны;зоны. 11.SEOВсе настройки SEO, такие как мета-название, мета-описания, мета ключевые слова, обратные ссылки, взаимные ссылки и т.д. также переносятся из старого магазина в новый. Вы можете сохранить свой высокий рейтинг SEO на Google и во всех других поисковых системах.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[migration_tools]]></tab><version><![CDATA[6.0.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.3.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.6.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[79.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[89.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[74.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge><badge label="Oфициальный cоздатель модулей"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/1325414-pprod/-prestashop.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/1325414-pbig/-prestashop.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[9064]]></id><name><![CDATA[dwfproductextrafields]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Additional fields & tabs Product Details]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Дополнительной информации и вкладок товара]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Add additional fields on the products, that can be put as tabs or variables and inserted wherever you want]]></description><author><![CDATA[ohmyweb!]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/product-tab/9064-additional-fields-tabs-product-details.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/9064.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Add additional fields on the products, that can be put as tabs or variables and inserted wherever you want]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Maximum customization of your products through this module]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.7.36]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[59.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Oфициальный cоздатель модулей"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/979203-pprod/additional-fields-tabs-product-details.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/979203-pbig/additional-fields-tabs-product-details.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[11345]]></id><name><![CDATA[pushoncart]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Average Cart Booster (Cross-selling)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Перекрестные продажи и Создание комплектов]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Мы приглашаем вас быстро увеличить средне-покупательную способность корзины ваших клиентов, благодаря специальной акции прекрасно адаптированной для покупательной способности ваших клиентов]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/cross-selling-product-bundles/11345-average-cart-booster-cross-selling.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/11345.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Мы приглашаем вас быстро увеличить средне-покупательную способность корзины ваших клиентов, благодаря специальной акции прекрасно адаптированной для покупательной способности ваших клиентов.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[свободное повышение средне-покупательной способности корзины ваших клиентов&nbsp;легкое сбывание запасов продуктов по вашему выбору&nbsp;дайте попробовать вашим клиентам те новые продукты, которые они может еще не знают, создавая потребность, и верность покупателя&nbsp;повышение удовлетворенности клиентов через акции приятно адаптированные к их потребностям]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[merchandizing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.3.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.1.5]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[79.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[89.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[64.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/595049-pprod/average-cart-booster-cross-selling.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/595049-pbig/average-cart-booster-cross-selling.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[13435]]></id><name><![CDATA[lgbannerhost]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Block Bots / Users based on IP, Country or User-Agent]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Безопасности и доступа]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Ban and block the access to your store for unwanted bots or users creating banishments by IP address, country code or user-agent]]></description><author><![CDATA[Línea Gráfica]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/website-security-access/13435-block-bots-users-based-on-ip-country-or-user-agent.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/13435.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Ban and block the access to your store for unwanted bots or users creating banishments by IP address, country code or user-agent.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[We have designed this module to help you prevent unwanted users from entering your store, especially robots, spiders, crawlers and shopping bots that may cause harm to you store. Ban by IP addressWrite the IP address you want to block and click on "Confirm". After that, the person with this IP will not be able to enter the website and will get a white page with the following message "Forbidden - You don't have permission to access ... on this server". You can create an unlimited number of IP bans.Note: you need to write the full IP address, this is NOT possible to use wildcard character such as * or % Ban by countryWrite the country code you want to block and click on "Confirm". After that, all the persons from this country will not be able to enter the website and will get a white page with the following message "Forbidden - You don't have permission to access ... on this server". You can create an unlimited number of country bans.Note: you need to have mod_geoip enabled on your server to be able to block users by country (you can ask your hosting to enable it for you). Ban by user-agentWrite the user-agent you want to block and click on "Confirm". After that, this user-agent will not be able to enter the website and will get a white page with the following message "Forbidden - You don't have permission to access ... on this server". You can create an unlimited number of user-agent bans. Some examples of user-agentsHere are some examples of user-agents: yandexbot, baiduspider, sogou spider, bingbot, slurp, msnbot, twengabot, shopzilla, taringa, facebook...You will easily find the name of the user-agents you are looking for at the following links:http://user-agent-string.info/list-of-ua/botshttp://www.useragentstring.com/pages/useragentstring.php IMPORTANT BEFORE BUY THE MODULE: Our module only works with the Apache’s module from GeoIp installed on your system, not with the GeoIp library from PHP. If you don’t have the Apache’s module needed our module will never work in your shop.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.1.6]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.5.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.6.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[29.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[34.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[27.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Oфициальный cоздатель модулей"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/690790-pprod/block-bots-users-based-on-ip-country-or-user-agent.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/690790-pbig/block-bots-users-based-on-ip-country-or-user-agent.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[13654]]></id><name><![CDATA[hspointofsalepro]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[RockPOS - Point of Sale and Omnichannel]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Кассовое ПО]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Since 2015, RockPOS has been the leading POS system for PrestaShop]]></description><author><![CDATA[Hamsa]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/point-of-sale-pos/13654-rockpos-point-of-sale-and-omnichannel.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/13654.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Since 2015, RockPOS has been the leading POS system for PrestaShop. RockPOS can speed up the check-out process, help online retailers with their physical stores, and unleash business owners’ full potential.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Speed-up selling: By connecting to barcode and printer, the user-friendly design of RockPOS allows you to check out with only a few clicks. With this fast service, there will be no longer a line of grumpy customers waiting for their check-out. &nbsp;Help you make informed decisions: RockPOS records all your sales and employee performance as well as the number of order. These records are automatically synchronized if you operate multiple stores. Insightfully, these records are valuable for strategic business decisions.Build customer relationship: By recording sales performance, you can determine different types of customers through sales patterns. From there, with RockPOS loyalty program, you can reward and motivate those most valuable customers, giving them reasons to come back.Grow your business: With trouble-free in installation and no extra fee, you can easily set up ROckPOS to run your physical store smoothly. With just a few clicks to add staff, items, location, your business is ready to run.Support with confidence: As a proud Superhero support ranking of Prestashop, we work toward our customers’ success. RockPOS support team is always ready to help.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[payments_gateways]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.1.14]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.1.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[299.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[339.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[269.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Oфициальный cоздатель модулей"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/884358-pprod/rockpos-point-of-sale-and-omnichannel.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/884358-pbig/rockpos-point-of-sale-and-omnichannel.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[16535]]></id><name><![CDATA[pscartabandonmentpro]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Abandoned Cart Pro]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Перенаправление и Брошенные корзины]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Improve your conversion rate by 15% (and more) with abandoned carts reminder emails!]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/remarketing-shopping-cart-abandonment/16535-abandoned-cart-pro.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/16535.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Improve your conversion rate by 15% (and more) with abandoned carts reminder emails!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[                                                              ]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[advertising_marketing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.0.5]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[119.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[134.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[109.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/920927-pprod/abandoned-cart-pro.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/920927-pbig/abandoned-cart-pro.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[16633]]></id><name><![CDATA[prettyurls]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Pretty URL - удаление идентификаторов и номеров из URL]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Управления адресами URL и перенаправлением]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Модуль расширенных URL-адресов PrestaShop делает ваши URL-адреса вашего магазина безопасными для SEO, удаляя автоматически сгенерированные идентификаторы/номера из URL-адресов ваших продуктов, категор]]></description><author><![CDATA[FME Modules]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/url-redirects/16633-pretty-url-url.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/16633.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Модуль расширенных URL-адресов PrestaShop делает ваши URL-адреса вашего магазина безопасными для SEO, удаляя автоматически сгенерированные идентификаторы/номера из URL-адресов ваших продуктов, категорий, производителей и других страниц.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Что предлагает этот модуль: Удаляет идентификаторы и номера из ваших URL-адресов магазина301 перенаправляет старые URL-адреса на новые URL-адресаПредоставляет двойной URL-адресЗадайте предпочтение URL-адресапродукта как с категориями, так и без них. Why Clean Urls Are Important For SEO - Read Guidelines By GOOGLE https://support.google.com/webmasters/answer/76329?hl=en  Вы хотите удалить идентификаторы из URL-адресов своего магазина PrestaShop, чтобы ссылки магазина электронной коммерции стали дружественными поисковыми системами, чтобы получить лучшее ранжирование в результатах поиска? Модуль КрасивыхURL-адресов PrestaShop автоматически удаляет созданные идентификаторы и номера из URL-адресов, чтобы они могли стать дружелюбными не только к пользователям, но и к поисковой системе для лучшего ранжирования. По умолчанию URL-адрес магазина PrestaShop содержит идентификаторы, которые не соответствуют рекомендациям, предоставляемым поисковыми системами. ПлагинКрасивыхURL-адресов PrestaShop может использоваться, чтобы сделать URL-адрес seo удобным для категорий, CMS, продуктов, поставщиков и производителей страниц. В основном динамически созданные URL-адреса бессмысленны, неактуальны, неинформативны и имеют меньший потенциал для более высоких рангов в результатах поиска. Именно поэтому модульпоиска красивых URL-адресов PrestaShop очищает URL-адреса, которые удобны для пользователя, а также дружественные поисковой системе, он заменяет случайно сгенерированные идентификаторы с адресов веб-сайтов. Вместо использования нерелевантных символов в адресе, например www.domain.com/1-product-A, надстройка очищает URL-адрес и добавляет имя продукта и услуги, предлагаемое на странице, например www.domain.com/product- A.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[seo]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.2.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.6.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[59.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Oфициальный cоздатель модулей"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/1269872-pprod/pretty-url-url.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/1269872-pbig/pretty-url-url.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[16939]]></id><name><![CDATA[seoexpert]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[SEO Expert]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Естественная поисковая оптимизация]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Increase site traffic by optimizing the position of your website on search engine results!  This SEO Expert module automatically fills in both meta tags and social media meta tags to optimize your onl]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/seo-natural-search-engine-optimization/16939-seo-expert.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/16939.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Increase site traffic by optimizing the position of your website on search engine results!  This SEO Expert module automatically fills in both meta tags and social media meta tags to optimize your online store for better visibility on search engines and social media platforms.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Automatically create meta tags to save over 40 hours! With the SEO Expert module:Appear on first page results on search engines like Google, Bing, Yahoo, Yandex, etc.Multiply your sales with increased web trafficImprove visibility for each language of your storeIncrease your conversions with qualified trafficDifferentiate your store with fully customized rules for product.Leverage Facebook and Twitter to acquire even more customersOptimize your online store for social media with adapted shared titles]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[seo]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.2.9]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[149.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[169.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[134.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/595316-pprod/seo-expert.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/595316-pbig/seo-expert.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[17711]]></id><name><![CDATA[totswitchattribute]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Enable / Disable a Combination, Import .csv]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Вариаций и персонализации товаров]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[This module allows you to disable a product attribute combinations (without deleting) and activate them whenever you want]]></description><author><![CDATA[202 ecommerce]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/combinaisons-product-customization/17711-enable-disable-a-combination-import-csv.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/17711.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[This module allows you to disable a product attribute combinations (without deleting) and activate them whenever you want. You can update combinations status quickly by importing a list of disabled products via .csv file.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA["Enable / Disable a Combination, Import .csv" allows you to disable a combination and then reactivate it when you want without deleting any information.Save time with this module when a product combination is not available or out of stock. Once a declination is temporarily unavailable, most dealers like to hide a combination to avoid frustrating customers. Unfortunately, it is not possible to disable a Prestashop combination (it is necessary to eliminate it). When the combination is available again, you must then recreate it, which is quite time consuming, especially if the above is composed of several attributes, or require a weight or price impact.Our module allows you simply disable combinations (which makes attribute invisible to your customers), and also to enable it at any time and to resume sales !There are two ways to disable/enable product combinations:- manual management,- mass combinations management via .csv import.Enable combinations as quickly as you disabled it: our module allows you to see the summary of disabled combinations and enable them at any time; it is also possible to reactivate combinations directly via product page.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.3.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.3.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[59.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Oфициальный cоздатель модулей"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/843379-pprod/enable-disable-a-combination-import-csv.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/843379-pbig/enable-disable-a-combination-import-csv.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[18016]]></id><name><![CDATA[supercheckout]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Knowband - One Page Checkout, Social Login & Mailchimp]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Процесс заказа]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Mobile responsive One Page Checkout with Facebook/Google+, MailChimp and Ship2Pay feature. It can be used with any theme & any payment method. Compatibility with 30+ Payment & Shipping Methods]]></description><author><![CDATA[Knowband]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/express-checkout-process/18016-knowband-one-page-checkout-social-login-mailchimp.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/18016.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Mobile responsive One Page Checkout with Facebook/Google+, MailChimp and Ship2Pay feature. It can be used with any theme & any payment method. Compatibility with 30+ Payment & Shipping Methods. This One Page Checkout Module is GDPR compliant.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[This one-page checkout module is a feature-packed addon for your store. It helps to reduce the checkout steps of the website.Let’s take a look at the functionality of this one-page checkout addon: Show/Hide any Fields: The store admin can decide which fields he/she want to display on the checkout page with the help of fast one-page checkout module. This quick checkout module has the functionality to show/hide fields like Company, VAT, Address title etc. Customize buttons: You can change your page buttons color to match them with your theme template by using color picker tool of responsive checkout module admin panel. No coding knowledge is required. You can do it in just a few clicks. GDPR Settings: The Prestashop Quick checkout addon offers the admin to add multiple checkboxes to get the customer consent before placing the order. Admin can also add the link to the Privacy Policy page. The admin can make any of the policies mandatory or optional for the customers. The simplified checkout addon allows the admin to edit or delete any policy whenever needed. Customer Consent: The quick checkout module Prestashop provides the e-merchants to record the customer consent along with the order reference id, email id, customer name, type of accepted consent, date as well as time too. The admin can check the desired customer consent just by entering the order reference id or email id. Mailchimp: The Prestashop store admin can send customer email id directly to Mailchimp either when customer come out from email field or when he places an order after selecting the checkbox for newsletter subscription. If any customer logins via social login options(Google or Facebook button), even then the email will be sent to Mailchimp. Change Shipping/Payment method name or image: This one-step checkout module allows the store admin to change the shipping/payment methods name or image easily without any change in the code. Make any field optional: There is an option in this responsive one-page checkout addon using which admin can make any field optional or mandatory. Sort address fields: The Prestashop store admin can also manage to sort all address fields using drag and drop feature. Example: Phone number field can be placed just before First name etc. Drag and Drop: You can change the position of all blocks using drag and drop features. You can also show payment method first and shipping method below as per the requirement. Ship2pay: Using this feature the store admin can disable payment methods based on customer shipping method selection. Custom CSS and JS: There is an option in admin panel to add custom CSS and JS. Admin can use this feature to make desired changes without editing core files of one step checkout addon. Custom HTML: This simplified checkout addon also has an option to add multiple custom HTML block at any place. Admin can promote any product, display any promotion OR provide any messages to our customers regarding deal, shipping or payment method information etc. Testing mode: The one-page checkout addon has a testing mode using which admins can test the module on their live site without affecting their ongoing business. If the testing mode is enabled, all customers will go to default checkout of Prestashop and admin can test the module page using a URL which will be shown in one step checkout module's admin side. FAQ tab: We understand the value of your time and therefore we have added all basic queries related to this quick checkout module in our admin panel so that you don't need to contact us for small issues/queries. Custom Fields: System Admin can add any number of custom fields on the checkout page.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[checkout]]></tab><version><![CDATA[5.0.7]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[79.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[89.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[74.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Oфициальный cоздатель модулей"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/882987-pprod/knowband-one-page-checkout-social-login-mailchimp.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/882987-pbig/knowband-one-page-checkout-social-login-mailchimp.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[18478]]></id><name><![CDATA[recaptcha]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[re Captcha - Anti Spam - recaptcha]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Безопасности и доступа]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Tired of receiving spam emails? Our module allows you to integrate Google protection on your registration and contact form. Spam emails are blocked. Your customers do not need to copy anti-robot code]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/website-security-access/18478-re-captcha-anti-spam-recaptcha.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/18478.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Tired of receiving spam emails? Our module allows you to integrate Google protection on your registration and contact form. Spam emails are blocked. Your customers do not need to copy anti-robot code.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Save time: deleting spamCaptcha system from Google, the user does not need to copy the code. The algorithm is based on the analysis of mouse movements.Enhanced Security&nbsp;The installation is simplified, you no longer need to place a line of code on your templates. Everything is automatic for Prestashop versions: 1.5, 1.6 and 1.7.For Prestashop 1.4, a line remains to be added to your contact form template.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.2.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.4.0.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[29.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[34.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[27.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/1008639-pprod/re-captcha-anti-spam-recaptcha.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/1008639-pbig/re-captcha-anti-spam-recaptcha.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[18656]]></id><name><![CDATA[jmarketplace]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[JA Marketplace]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Создания торговой площадки]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Create your own marketplace allowing your customers register as sellers for sell their products in exchange for a commission]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/marketplace-creation/18656-ja-marketplace.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/18656.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Create your own marketplace allowing your customers register as sellers for sell their products in exchange for a commission.  ]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Best module of Spain in PrestaShop Awards 2015. Module that allows create a marketplace with PrestaShop from multiple vendors. All sellers in the same market. Create a market in your PrestaShop store practically 100% configurable where you can enable and disable all the fields of the forms and many other options. Discover it with all the information that we detail on this page and visit the demo site to see it work. It is also ideal to see the screenshots and the video to see all the details. This module allows you to integrate several shops in the same economic platform and common retail space. All members can benefit from the sales force other vendors to obtain greater visibility increasing the number of customers and sales. This integration of sale is currently one of the most effective ways to compete with traditional large surfaces and large ecommerce operators (Amazon, eBay, etc.). With this module you can join in their market strength of different suppliers to have more visibility and more sales. Creating a market in PrestaShop is quick and easy with JA Marketplace and your module complementaries. The configuration is very complete and intuitive. You can enable and disable functions for vendors with ease but, what makes this module more powerful is its technical versatility and scalability thanks to its hooks or positions to incorporate new functions for sellers.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[6.1.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.6.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[199.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[224.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[179.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/1338896-pprod/ja-marketplace.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/1338896-pbig/ja-marketplace.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[18850]]></id><name><![CDATA[orderedit]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Order Edit - Change and Modify existing order]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Управление заказами]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[With this module you can modify and alter every existing order in your store, also after the purchase is completed]]></description><author><![CDATA[Silbersaiten]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/order-management/18850-order-edit-change-and-modify-existing-order.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/18850.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[With this module you can modify and alter every existing order in your store, also after the purchase is completed. ]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Articles information, shipping information, payments and discounts can be modified. Please refer to the screens, the video, the demoshop, or contact us directly in order to get more information on how the module works.  ]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.3.17]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[59.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[69.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[54.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Oфициальный cоздатель модулей"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/714564-pprod/order-edit-change-and-modify-existing-order.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/714564-pbig/order-edit-change-and-modify-existing-order.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[19062]]></id><name><![CDATA[layerslider]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Creative Slider - Responsive Slideshow]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Слайдеров (карусельных) и галерей]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Creative Slider is a premium multi-purpose slider to create image galleries, content sliders, and mind-blowing slideshows with must-see effects]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/sliders-galleries/19062-creative-slider-responsive-slideshow.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/19062.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Creative Slider is a premium multi-purpose slider to create image galleries, content sliders, and mind-blowing slideshows with must-see effects. It uses cutting edge technologies to provide the smoothest experience that’s possible. ]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Creative Slider comes with more than 200 preset 2D and 3D slide transitions. It has a beautiful and easy-to-use admin interface with supporting modern features like drag 'n’ drop WYSIWYG slider builder, real-time previews, timeline view, Google Fonts and transition builder for custom animations. It’s device friendly by supporting responsive mode, multiple layouts, touch gestures on mobile devices, and uses techniques like lazy load and conditional script loading for optimal performance. You can add any content into sliders, including images, text, custom HTML, YouTube and Vimeo videos or HTML5 self-hosted multimedia contents. It’s also SEO friendly by allowing you to build semantic markup with custom attributes that search engines can index easily. Creative Slider comes with 13 built-in skins, and it hastons of options to entirely customize the appearance and behavior of your sliders at the smallest detail.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[slideshows]]></tab><version><![CDATA[6.6.6]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.17]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.6.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[44.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[39.99]]></GBP></price><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/948729-pprod/creative-slider-responsive-slideshow.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/948729-pbig/creative-slider-responsive-slideshow.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[19431]]></id><name><![CDATA[prestanotifypro]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Pop Promo (Popup)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Всплывающие окна]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Increase the effectiveness of your promotions tenfold and sell more!  This pop-in can be configured in less than a minute, which attracts the attention of your visitors]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/pop-up/19431-pop-promo-popup.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/19431.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Increase the effectiveness of your promotions tenfold and sell more!  This pop-in can be configured in less than a minute, which attracts the attention of your visitors. It allows you to immediately grasp the attention to whatever you wish, inform and make your promotions, sales and flash sales a success.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Increase your conversions during promotions as well as subscriptions to your newsletter by 20% to 1,000%Make additional sales in the category of your choice.Launch your new products successfully by making them unmissableOne minute is all it takes to configure this module, you can therefore be highly responsive at all times or schedule your campaigns in advanceDistinguish and identify items with low activity sales, which allows you to promote, sell and replace to make room for your new collections.&nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.2.8]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.3.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[44.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[29.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/926172-pprod/pop-promo-popup.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/926172-pbig/pop-promo-popup.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[19584]]></id><name><![CDATA[tacartreminder]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Smart Cart Reminder]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Перенаправление и Брошенные корзины]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[More than 18% conversion observed in several e-retailers who have adopted it]]></description><author><![CDATA[TimActive]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/remarketing-shopping-cart-abandonment/19584-smart-cart-reminder.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/19584.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[More than 18% conversion observed in several e-retailers who have adopted it. The advanced solution for the abandoned cart reminder is what will fit your reminder emails, your promotions to your customers&#39; cart.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[According to the abandoned cart content, and information about the customers, the Smart Cart Reminder module is the advanced solution that allows you to remind your abandoned carts in an autonomous and focused way.  &laquo;&nbsp;The only module of the cart reminder without subscription offering as many features&nbsp;&raquo; &nbsp;** EMAILS OF REMINDER AND OFFERS ABOUT MARKETING ADAPTED TO EACH CART ** Indeed, the module allows you to create &quot;Reminder rules&quot; according to:Customer information (country, age, gender, group, etc.)Cart contents (amount, products, product categories, stock remaining, etc.)Time of year (Christmas, New Year&rsquo;s, Valentine&rsquo;s Day, Mothers&rsquo; Day, etc.) &laquo;&nbsp;No more untimely and inappropriate promotions which let you feel that you are desperate !&nbsp;&raquo;  With the reminder rules, create easily your own algorithms, for example:  Rule 1&nbsp;: For the cart that exceeds $90, which still contain available items in my stock, the customer is in USA. Then create a discount coupon to obtain the shipping costs for free. Reminder1: Send the &laquo;&nbsp;Free shipping costs&nbsp;&raquo; email. Reminder2: Send the &laquo;&nbsp;Only a few days to benefit from the offer&raquo; email. ------------ Rule 2: For the new customers, create a 5% Off Your Order. Reminder1: 1H after the dropped cart: send the &laquo;To celebrate your arrival 5% Off Your First Order &raquo; email. Reminder2: 24H after Reminder 1: send the &laquo;&nbsp;Only one day left to take advantage of this offer&raquo; email. ------------ Rule 3: From 15/11/2015 to 25/12/2015(Christmas time), create a coupon to obtain a gift on the order. Reminder 1: Send the &laquo;&nbsp;Surprise Gift&raquo; email. Reminder 2: Send the &laquo;&nbsp;Only a few days to benefit from the offer&raquo; email. ------------ Rule 4: For the cart &gt; &euro;900, the customer is professional Reminder 1: Send the &laquo;&nbsp;More information about our catalog dedicated to professional&raquo; email. Reminder 2: Contact the customer by phone  My interest through Smart Cart Reminder module and the reminder rules: &rarr; &nbsp;I increase my sales &rarr; &nbsp;I control the cost of my marketing offers according to the cart &rarr; &nbsp;I approach as close as possible to the desire of my customers &rarr; &nbsp;I gain credibility by creating an intelligent and autonomous system which is no longer seen by my customers as an automatic emails or promotion distributor.  &nbsp;** MANY KINDS OF REMINDER &laquo;&nbsp;STANDARD&raquo; or &laquo;MANUAL&raquo; **&nbsp;Two kinds of reminders to adapt a little more to your reminder process:&laquo;Standard&raquo;: Sending an automatic email with a custom content of the cart to the customer.&laquo;&nbsp;Manual&raquo;: The module notifies you by email to communicate with the customer.You can even set the type of reminder that will suit your cart.  &nbsp;** AN INTERFACE DEDICATED TO &nbsp;&laquo;&nbsp;MANUAL &raquo; REMINDERS (PHONE) **&nbsp;In one page, the module includes all the information of your customers; and includes many features dedicated for your manual reminders.  My interest through&nbsp;my module &laquo;&nbsp;Smart Cart Reminder&nbsp;&raquo; and its page dedicated for manual reminders: &rarr; &nbsp;I don&rsquo;t lose anymore my customers information enabling me converting ( phone number, address, page visited, number of orders placed, current cart &hellip;) &rarr; I win in reactivity through the features present in this unique page: Sending a Pre-formatted email with the link of the complete order, creation of good (s) reduction (s) &rarr; I comment all my telephone conversations  &nbsp;** ADVANCED STATISTICS&nbsp;** &nbsp;The module provides a group of advanced reports easy-to-understand:The evolution of the generated sales according to cart remindersReports about the opened/clicked emailsCart reminder rule conversion reportsReports on employees manually remind customers. This report contains&nbsp;the number of orders made, the number of manual reminder processed for each employee. My interest through statistics is to improve me reminder system: &rarr; &nbsp;I improve my reminder emails to convert the maximum of cart &rarr; &nbsp;I improve my rules to build an autonomous system &rarr; &nbsp;I motivate my employees to increase my sales  &nbsp;** AN INTUITIVE AND EASY MODULE&nbsp;TO TAKE IN CHARGE ** &nbsp;&laquo;&nbsp;A quick start: Coming from a study conducted in the comb to a Committee of a dozen merchants, the module provides a clear and pleasant interface to use. Because we are committed to place the e-trader at the center of the process when we design our modules&raquo;  The module provides a range of features allowing you to act directly on the abandoned cart, you can manually raise without even that the countdown is finished, see explicit details of the choice of a rule for a cart...  My interest through its intuitive and transparent interface &nbsp;&nbsp; I spot in one glance: &rarr; The rules applied on the cart on each abandoned cart &rarr; The time left before the next reminder through the countdown &rarr; The list of reminders applied on the cart &rarr; If the reminder email was been seen and clicked &rarr; If the order was completed &rarr; &nbsp;...  &nbsp;** AN OPERATIONAL MODULE IN SOME CLICKS! ** &nbsp;1 Installation in 1 click and intuitive setting in 2 steps:1. I created my reminder emails, it&rsquo;s easy and fast! Several templates of emails delivered with the module, customize easily and quickly, select an example, edit the colors, edit the text, and here we go! 2- I create my cart reminder rules and I indicate for each rule the reminder emails to send.&nbsp;&nbsp;** A SUPPORT AT YOUR SERVICE&nbsp;**&laquo;Because your time is precious and that we want your full satisfaction!&nbsp;&raquo; &nbsp;You have particular difficulty for the integration, you have some questions. Our team will be glad to support you. We are very sensitive about the responsiveness and the quality of our responses. &nbsp; Source &laquo;&nbsp;addons.prestashop.com&nbsp;&raquo;:&nbsp; From 09/2013 to 08/2015&nbsp; Tickets received: 362 Handled: 362 Our overall service quality: 99.7% ** THEY BOUGHT THE MODULE AND YOU?**  20/08/2015 &laquo;Your module is terrific!!!&nbsp;&raquo;  15/08/2015 - 5/5 &laquo;Great module and great support!&nbsp;&raquo;  28/07/2015 - 5/5 Lots of options to help increase sales. Very friendly and responsive customer service. Highly recommended!  15/07/2015 - 5/5 Very good quality, congratulation.  &laquo;&nbsp;I tried the challenge and I am pleased, congratulations to the developers of this module.&nbsp; I like your system customizing email, this is top!&nbsp;&raquo; Cathy  &laquo;&nbsp;I&#39;m a merchant since 8 years ago, and I gave some ideas. In fact I wanted a new condition to treat new customers differently and according to my stock. A module that I don&rsquo;t leave no more! What flexibility! I paid the purchase in the first week. &raquo;&nbsp;Audrey&laquo;&nbsp;Don&rsquo;t hesitate to share with us your comments!&raquo;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[advertising_marketing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.58]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.6.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[149.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[169.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[134.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Oфициальный cоздатель модулей"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/668257-pprod/smart-cart-reminder.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/668257-pbig/smart-cart-reminder.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[19749]]></id><name><![CDATA[flashsalepro]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Premium Flash Sale]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Закрытых и рекламных распродаж]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Multiply your shop sales using Flash Sales! Customisable and ideal for generating impulse buys, the Premium Flash Sales module increases your conversion rate and allows easy destocking]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/private-sales-flash-sales/19749-premium-flash-sale.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/19749.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Multiply your shop sales using Flash Sales! Customisable and ideal for generating impulse buys, the Premium Flash Sales module increases your conversion rate and allows easy destocking. &nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Increase your transformation rate by up to 59% thanks to flash sales!Boost your sales by giving your offers maximum visibilityLiquidate your stocks quickly and effectively to economise on storage costsLiven up your online shop easily and encourage your visitors to return to your store regularlyEncourage your indecisive customers to complete their purchases quickly because of the very limited duration of the offer and the countdown&nbsp; &nbsp; Expert tip: Send a newsletter to your customers to tell them about your flash sales using Official MailChimp (56% of businesses say they have a higher newsletter opening rate during flash sale periods) or inform your visitors when they reach your site thanks to a Pop Promo!]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[pricing_promotion]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.2.16]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[99.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[109.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[79.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/905699-pprod/premium-flash-sale.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/905699-pbig/premium-flash-sale.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[19959]]></id><name><![CDATA[pqshippingcostsbasedonzipcodes]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Shipping Costs per Zipcode, Zone, Country, State, City]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Стоимость доставки]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[This module allows you to configure and apply different shipping fees based on zipcodes of your customers]]></description><author><![CDATA[ProQuality]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/shipping-costs/19959-shipping-costs-per-zipcode-zone-country-state-city.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/19959.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[This module allows you to configure and apply different shipping fees based on zipcodes of your customers.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Prestashop gives  you the possibility to apply different shipping fees based on country or state, but in reality most of the carriers apply their shipping costs based on zipcodes because they can better control the territory (some charge higher fees for mountains or remote areas).  With this module you can improve your shipping system by setting up shipping fees based on your customers zipcodes. In order to do that you can easily use the zone system integrated in prestashop and cut a country in as many parts you want, then setup the shipping codes for each zone.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[shipping_logistics]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.0.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[59.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Oфициальный cоздатель модулей"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/1263977-pprod/shipping-costs-per-zipcode-zone-country-state-city.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/1263977-pbig/shipping-costs-per-zipcode-zone-country-state-city.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[20242]]></id><name><![CDATA[bridgeconnector]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Bridge Connector for Store Manager]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Быстрое & массовое редактирование]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Bridge Connector allows you to connect Store Manager application to PrestaShop Cloud and perform advanced data update and input (import, export, mass edit, etc)]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/mass-updates/20242-bridge-connector-for-store-manager.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/20242.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Bridge Connector allows you to connect Store Manager application to PrestaShop Cloud and perform advanced data update and input (import, export, mass edit, etc). Should be used with Store Manager desktop application]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Merchants will get access to their&nbsp;PrestaShop Cloud database with the help of Store Manager and perform the following operations: - Work with categories and products on a single page - no reload required; - Change prices of multiple products at the same time (perfect for sales!); - Create product features and combinations in bulk; - Upload multiple images simultaneously (drag and drop directly onto the browser); - Quickly update your inventory, manage stock levels, warehouses, and stock movements; - Import products (including virtual), specific prices, multi-features, attribute values, customized fields, and combinations; - Import products from csv, txt, xml, xls/xslx (Excel), ods (OpenOffice). No file requirements - all missing data can be applied on the fly; - Import customers with passwords exported from another PrestaShop installation (requires additional assistance); - Create orders with a POS and process them in bulk (e.g. change status for multiple orders at once); - Use store diagnostics to fix missing or broken images; - Take advantage of powerful reporting features; - Manage multiple PrestaShop installations and shops with one back-office; - Work offline - all changes will be applied when you reconnect.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[quick_bulk_update]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.0.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.1.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[29.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[34.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[27.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Oфициальный cоздатель модулей"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/691041-pprod/bridge-connector-for-store-manager.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/691041-pbig/bridge-connector-for-store-manager.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[20343]]></id><name><![CDATA[configurator]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Advanced configurator for customized product]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Вариаций и персонализации товаров]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Make available custom products !  Revolution avoiding duplicative combinations ! The customer see price updated in real time according to his choice]]></description><author><![CDATA[DM Concept]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/combinaisons-product-customization/20343-advanced-configurator-for-customized-product.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/20343.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Make available custom products !  Revolution avoiding duplicative combinations ! The customer see price updated in real time according to his choice.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[ You've certainly enough to multiply and above versions you are afraid of making mistakes , this module is for you . His conditional step by variations management system is ideal for composing a multi- level problem-free product. Example of use : Sale of customized door, window sale of tiles with specific size creation request quote with iterative choice ...]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[4.9.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.1.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.6.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[199.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[224.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[179.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Oфициальный cоздатель модулей"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/732490-pprod/advanced-configurator-for-customized-product.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/732490-pbig/advanced-configurator-for-customized-product.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[20451]]></id><name><![CDATA[pm_productsbyattributes]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Products by Attributes]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Вариаций и персонализации товаров]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Enhance your list pages by displaying the product variants linked to one or several attributes]]></description><author><![CDATA[Presta-Module]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/combinaisons-product-customization/20451-products-by-attributes.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/20451.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Enhance your list pages by displaying the product variants linked to one or several attributes]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[AN ESSENTIAL MERCHANDISING TOOL Show the combinations of your products from the category page (or any other page that lists products if your PrestaShop version is higher than 1.7.1) and boost your conversion rate by allowing your visitors to access more quickly the variant that matches their needs (size, color, shape, ...). Clicking on the chosen combination will direct them to the related product page and automatically pre-load the correct attributes values. Just a click on the "add to cart" button and it's done! Moreover, if some categories in your catalog suffer from a reduced number of products but that these have variants, our module will allow you to automatically enrich these pages. AN AMAZING ATTRIBUTES MANAGEMENT NEW!&nbsp;Our module now allows you to select&nbsp;several attributes&nbsp;from which to split the display of your products. Choose from all your attributes and combine them at will to get the best display of your product variants.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.0.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.6.3]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[59.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[69.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[54.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Oфициальный cоздатель модулей"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/695201-pprod/products-by-attributes.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/695201-pbig/products-by-attributes.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[20844]]></id><name><![CDATA[productlabel]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Product Label]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Бейджи и Логотипы]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/labels-stickers/20844-product-label.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/20844.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.2.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[69.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[79.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[54.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/1039434-pprod/product-label.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/1039434-pbig/product-label.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[20903]]></id><name><![CDATA[simplesitemap]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Sitemap Simple (Multishop, Multilang & Blogs)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Естественная поисковая оптимизация]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Sitemap (mult-shop and multi-language), incorporating various blogging modules ! Get rid of an important point by combining SEO and simplicity thanks to this sitemap module ! It’s a plug and play modu]]></description><author><![CDATA[Malttt]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/seo-natural-search-engine-optimization/20903-sitemap-simple-multishop-multilang-blogs.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/20903.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Sitemap (mult-shop and multi-language), incorporating various blogging modules ! Get rid of an important point by combining SEO and simplicity thanks to this sitemap module ! It’s a plug and play module ! Compliant with Google standards !  ]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[  Updated in real time with the latest published pages, fully customizable (you can block specific pages), it will load (for scheduled task) to prevent search engines at desired intervals. This module is multi-language and multishop: All your pages are indexed and listed in the languages ​​defined for each store/.  You can also include images or not, as you can turn off   Sitemap of or remove a link of it. It will also prevent robots (Google among others) the presence of it. It requires no special set-up action and adapts to any environment. Once installed, it's over, it works! No need to think about it! Easily customize the frequency of pages contained in the Sitemap. Automatic priority management is performed, calculated based on website updates.  It's necessary to stabilize a SEO / proper referencing in the ruthless world of the web, it will be an ideal and discreet companion, easy to implement. Simple, effective and very useful, this module is what all modules should do : a good job.  Sitemaps identified all sections of PrestaShop (products, categories, modules, CMS, rewrited URL's and suppliers). Implementation of Blogging modules within separates (for posts and categories) sitemaps too. Optimized SEO / SEO (Google / Bing / Yandex ) to make rapid progress your site to the top. Plug & Play : Once installed, it's ready ! Images included Separate Sitemaps for each shop and each containing selected languages ​​(multi-shop & multi-language) Support 24/7 to your every needs !]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[seo]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.3.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.2.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.6.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[99.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[114.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[89.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Oфициальный cоздатель модулей"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/716855-pprod/sitemap-simple-multishop-multilang-blogs.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/716855-pbig/sitemap-simple-multishop-multilang-blogs.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[21273]]></id><name><![CDATA[pqeasypost]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Easy Post Pro (DHL, GLS, DPD, Colissimo, RoyalMail etc)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Подготовка и отправка]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[This module allows you to significaly increase the speed of your shipping process by integrating EasyPost]]></description><author><![CDATA[ProQuality]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/preparation-shipping/21273-easy-post-pro-dhl-gls-dpd-colissimo-royalmail-etc.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/21273.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[This module allows you to significaly increase the speed of your shipping process by integrating EasyPost.com API (Application Programming Interface) into PrestaShop and printing your shipping labels fast and easy. Only 3 cents per label!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[We all know that in order to run a successful business you have to optimize it and automatize it as much as possible, this module allows you to do that by increasing the shipping process by 70%.   Think of how long it takes to receive an order from your customers, process the order by adding the products to the package, then connect to your shipping carrier`s software and manually insert the customer information, parcel information and delivery address for the order, for each order at a time. This is very time consuming and it`s very easy to make mistakes because you have a lot of data to process.  With this module all of this is done automatically via the API (Application Programming Interface) that connects the orders section in prestashop with the carrier and instantly sends the information to the carrier, then prints the shipping label which is then slicked to the package. The module supports the most important carriers in the world.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[shipping_logistics]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.8.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[59.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[69.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[54.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Oфициальный cоздатель модулей"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/726515-pprod/easy-post-pro-dhl-gls-dpd-colissimo-royalmail-etc.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/726515-pbig/easy-post-pro-dhl-gls-dpd-colissimo-royalmail-etc.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[21278]]></id><name><![CDATA[popnewsletter]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Popup Newsletter]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Всплывающие окна]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[The most effective way to stay in touch with your customers! Pop Newsletter creates a popup inviting your visitors to sign up for your newsletter]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/pop-up/21278-popup-newsletter.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/21278.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[The most effective way to stay in touch with your customers! Pop Newsletter creates a popup inviting your visitors to sign up for your newsletter. With this professional and completely customisable pop-up, you can attract new subscribers and retain them with a discount on their next purchase.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Pop Newsletter allows you to show your visitors a pop-in when they arrive in your shop. Turn your visitors into subscribers! &nbsp; Improve the subscription rate for your shop:  Pop-ins are effective at attracting visitors&rsquo; attention, gaining more clicks than sliders, banners or sign-up panels in the footer (which have a conversion rate of only 0.05%). The proven results for this tool show increases of between 20% and 1,000% in your subscription rate. &nbsp; Turn your subscribers into loyal customers: Offer them a discount voucher for their next purchase in your shop to thank them for subscribing. &nbsp; Offer a flawless user experience: Similar to pop-ups but with an improved user experience, pop-ins integrate perfectly with the page where they appear. Pop Newsletter applies best practices recommended for this advertising method:Lightbox effectOption to close the module window with a simple click outside the pop-in, as well as a cross symbol button for closure in the top right-hand corner.Option to specify when the pop-in is activated. This allows your visitor to get to know your site before seeing the pop-in.Once your visitor closes the pop-in, it will not be shown again.Adaptable to all types of shop, with no need for programming or graphic design skills.&nbsp; &nbsp; Improve results from your newsletters by increasing your contact base: Thanks to the optional newsletter sign-up form, you can analyse and classify your subscribers more effectively. Pop Newsletter also allows you to send a confirmation e-mail to the e-mail address provided by your subscriber to ensure there is no chance of your newsletter being sent to an incorrect address.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.5.8]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[59.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[69.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/722395-pprod/popup-newsletter.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/722395-pbig/popup-newsletter.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[21318]]></id><name><![CDATA[magicredirect]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Redirections URL (301 / Auto-fixing / Multishop / SEO)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Управления адресами URL и перенаправлением]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Predicts and automatically fix missing pages ! Easily manage all your missing pages and your referrals (404, 301 etc) on your shop (Multi-shop & languages ready)]]></description><author><![CDATA[Malttt]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/url-redirects/21318-redirections-url-301-auto-fixing-multishop-seo.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/21318.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Predicts and automatically fix missing pages ! Easily manage all your missing pages and your referrals (404, 301 etc) on your shop (Multi-shop & languages ready). Automaticly redirect disabled and deleted front office pages !]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Magic Redirect saves you valuable time by doing for you most actions concerning your redirections (301) and your pages not found (404):Automaticly redirect any disabled/deleted object (products, manufacturers, suppliers, categories, cms pages and categories) to natural parent page.Be warned each new error, but is not intrusive.The module attempts to find internal links that could address these issues. You then have to activate them on the fly.Lead your customers more easily to the right pages.Create rules in the event of major changes on your shop.Lost pages are pre-filled to facilitate your work.Improve your SEO everyday. Google grants a bonus to websites regulating their 404!]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[seo]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.3.6]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.2.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.6.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[59.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Oфициальный cоздатель модулей"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/723026-pprod/redirections-url-301-auto-fixing-multishop-seo.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/723026-pbig/redirections-url-301-auto-fixing-multishop-seo.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[21510]]></id><name><![CDATA[popexit]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Pop Exit]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Всплывающие окна]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Make a pop-up appear when your visitors are about to leave your site, and encourage them to complete their order!  Thanks to the Pop Exit module, win back 25% of visitors who are about to leave by off]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/pop-up/21510-pop-exit.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/21510.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Make a pop-up appear when your visitors are about to leave your site, and encourage them to complete their order!  Thanks to the Pop Exit module, win back 25% of visitors who are about to leave by offering them a very appealing temporary (or permanent) reduction.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Reduce your abandoned carts by capturing your visitors when they are about to leave your site by encouraging them to complete their purchases;Improve your store&#39;s conversion rate by offering your visitors a temporary reduction to encourage them to make their purchase;Create an effective and attractive on-site retargeting tool in less than 5 minutes using the professional designs available to you and the easy-to-configure module.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.16]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.1.5]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[69.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[79.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[54.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/727469-pprod/pop-exit.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/727469-pbig/pop-exit.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[22666]]></id><name><![CDATA[onlinechat]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Online Chat]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Поддержка и онлайн-чат]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[With the Online Chat module developed by PrestaShop, you can finally offer an online chat system on your shop to have discussions with your customers]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/support-online-chat/22666-online-chat.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/22666.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[With the Online Chat module developed by PrestaShop, you can finally offer an online chat system on your shop to have discussions with your customers. This communication tool has become vital for e-commerce stores and allows you to create stronger relationships with your customers by guiding and advising them in their purchases in real time.   With this module that requires no subscription, improve your customer relations and your after-sales services, while increasing your conversion rate by up to 40%!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[No subscription needed; in just a few clicks you can set up your module and begin conversing with your online customers!&nbsp;You will find a simple, easy-to-use, responsive&nbsp;interface and a design that adapts perfectly to your site, in administration as for your store.&nbsp;With online conversations, you build a stronger, more human relationship with your customers and improve loyalty to your brand.&nbsp;You reduce the number of abandoned carts by answering your visitors&rsquo; questions directly.&nbsp;You save time in managing after-sales services by solving problems and requests live.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.0.6]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[79.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[94.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[64.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/752296-pprod/online-chat.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/752296-pbig/online-chat.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[22777]]></id><name><![CDATA[savvysearch]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Savvy Search Autocomplete]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Поиск и фильтры]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Отличный модуль поиска с автодополнением, который упростит использование любого магазина и значительно повысит продажи]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/search-filters/22777-savvy-search-autocomplete.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/22777.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Отличный модуль поиска с автодополнением, который упростит использование любого магазина и значительно повысит продажи. При вводе ключевых слов модуль предлагает соответствующие товары с фотографиями и описаниями, атрибуты, теги, категории, и др.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Savvy Search Autocomplete станет сильной стороной вашего интернет-магазина, привлекая клиентов и улучшая их впечатление от вашего сайта. Модуль показывает данные, имеющие отношение к вводимому запросу (ключевым словам), а это сразу укажет на то, что вашему магазину есть что предложить покупателю. Модуль также обеспечивает быстрый доступ к искомым категориям и продуктам. Если пользователь может получить ожидаемый результат быстро &mdash; это ускоряет покупку и оставляет клиенту лучшие впечатления от вашего интернет-магазина.&nbsp;Панель управления модуля обеспечивает большое количество настроек, для управления всеми аспектами функциональности и отображения результатов. В их числе настройки алгоритма, показываемые данные и т.п.&nbsp;Модуль выглядит отлично без дополнительных настроек, и может быть запущен в течение нескольких минут. Дополнительно панель администратора включает в себя возможности, которые позволяют настраивать внешний вид модуля, изменяя цвета его элементов.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[search_filter]]></tab><version><![CDATA[5.1.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.1.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[59.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Best Module Navigation"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/awards-navigation.png]]></badge><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/770080-pprod/savvy-search-autocomplete.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/770080-pbig/savvy-search-autocomplete.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[22779]]></id><name><![CDATA[sizeconversion]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Size Guide]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Размеры]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/sizes-units/22779-size-guide.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/22779.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.2.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[59.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[69.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[54.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/755429-pprod/size-guide.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/755429-pbig/size-guide.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[23426]]></id><name><![CDATA[hsmultiaccessoriespro]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Multi Accessories Pro]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Перекрестные продажи и Создание комплектов]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[&nbsp;Multi Accessories builds a flexible bundle of products]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/cross-selling-product-bundles/23426-multi-accessories-pro.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/23426.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[&nbsp;Multi Accessories builds a flexible bundle of products.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Offer a bundle of products, therefore increase sales amazingly.Does it sounds like combinations? Yes, it seems, but it&#39;s totally different. A product and its accessories are separated products, they are not different attributes of the product.Does it also sounds like a packed product? Yes, it seems too. But your customers are free to choose one or more or even not choose any accessories to be checked out. It&#39;s very flexible.Don&#39;t you see any differences in compare to built-in accessory feature? Alright, it&#39;s very similar to, but instead of adding accessories, now you can add them in different groups of accessories. This is a good suggestion for your customers in case they don&#39;t know what to buy with.And what about related product feature? Accessories are a kind of &quot;related&quot; and more structural.Beyond all of them, shopping has never been easy like this. Just choose accessories and click &quot;Add to basket&quot;. All of accessories and the main product now are already in the shopping cart!]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[merchandizing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.2.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.6.2]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[99.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[114.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[89.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Best Module Average Cart"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/awards-average-cart.png]]></badge><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/764826-pprod/multi-accessories-pro.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/764826-pbig/multi-accessories-pro.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[23517]]></id><name><![CDATA[pm_easyplaces]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Easy Places]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Pегистрации и оформления заказа]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Easy Places is the fastest and easiest way to offer your customers an address autofill feature]]></description><author><![CDATA[Presta-Module]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/registration-ordering-process/23517-easy-places.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/23517.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Easy Places is the fastest and easiest way to offer your customers an address autofill feature. Help your customers save time and reduce the number of customers who give up whilst creating an account from now on!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Our Easy Places module helps you increase your transformation rate by simplifying the order creation process, by providing a feature that automatically enters the account creation or order addresses.  - "OK, but why do I need that ?" - When a new customer wants to place an order on your shop, you have to ask them for their delivery and invoicing address. Your customers find this compulsory and repetitive step annoying and frustrating. Some customers give up and go to another site where they know they have already entered all their information. What is more, shipping errors caused by customers entering their addresses incorrectly are not uncommon, entailing additional transport costs and decreased customer satisfaction owing to the delays caused by their parcels being sent out and returned again.  Easy Places is the ultimate solution for avoiding such problems! It allows you to offer your clients an elegant, high performance technical solution to make your account creation forms more pleasant to fill in.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[checkout]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.5]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[44.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[39.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Oфициальный cоздатель модулей"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/766068-pprod/easy-places.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/766068-pbig/easy-places.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[23617]]></id><name><![CDATA[zendesk]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Official Zendesk]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Послепродажное обслуживание]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Contextualize your customer interactions by seeing their latest orders when managing tickets inside Zendesk]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/customer-service/23617-official-zendesk.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/23617.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Contextualize your customer interactions by seeing their latest orders when managing tickets inside Zendesk. Order details such as status, total, creation date, and products names and quantities are all visible from within Zendesk.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[&nbsp;This integration will save customer support agents time and contextualize interactions as they no longer need to switch between Prestashop and Zendesk&#39;s interfaces to link a ticket to customer orders.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.1.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.3.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/976308-pprod/official-zendesk.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/976308-pbig/official-zendesk.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[23671]]></id><name><![CDATA[facebookproductad]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Dynamic Ads + Pixel]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Перенаправление и Брошенные корзины]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Export on Facebook shop, create product ads, identify on Instagram, make tracking]]></description><author><![CDATA[Business Tech]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/remarketing-shopping-cart-abandonment/23671-dynamic-ads-pixel.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/23671.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Export on Facebook shop, create product ads, identify on Instagram, make tracking]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[* * * WINNER OF THE 2017 PRESTASHOP AWARDS CEREMONY FOR THE BEST MODULE * * *&nbsp;EXPORT A HIGH QUALITY PRODUCT FEED ON FACEBOOK &nbsp;The &quot;Dynamic Ads + Pixel&quot; module allows you to configure your data feed in an extremely simple and fast way by including only the products and information you want. The advanced exclusion rules system gives you the freedom to create an optimized feed by excluding certain products from your ads. The advanced assignment of custom labels to your products further increases the customization of your data feed and allows you to increase the segmentation possibilities of your catalog.&nbsp;Product feeds generated and imported in the Facebook Business Manager will allow you:&nbsp;to automatically supply and keep updated&nbsp;the shop section of your Facebook pageto diffuse&nbsp;product ads&nbsp;on Facebook and Instagram for very targeted audiencesto identify your products&nbsp;in your Facebook and Instagram publications or stories&nbsp;&nbsp;TAKE ADVANTAGE OF THE WORLD&#39;S MOST ADVANCED ADVERTISING TECHNOLOGY&nbsp;Thanks to countless personal information collected on its network, each more accurate than the others, Facebook has&nbsp;a powerful advertising targeting tool&nbsp;on which Google can not compete. On the Business Manager interface you have a multitude of options allowing you to create your advertising audiences according to age, sex, family situation, geographical location, interests, groups, liked pages and any other information that Facebook has about its users.&nbsp;By installing a tracking tag (Facebook pixel) on your site pages, our module allows you to&nbsp;further&nbsp;enhance these audiences. Indeed, this pixel allows you to create audiences based on&nbsp;your visitor activity (purchases, products seen, carts,...).&nbsp;It also allows you to enjoy the indisputable efficiency of&nbsp;dynamic retargeting. Thus, you can for example to launch ad campaigns that will automatically display to Facebook users, the products they previously viewed on your site, or relevant product recommandations. Business Manager tools will then allow you to analyse the efficiency of these ads (conversion tracking).&nbsp;The power of Facebook also allows you&nbsp;to acquire new customers&nbsp;by attracting people whose interests are close to your current customers. Indeed, the personal information of the social network users, own by Facebook, is compared to the one of your existing customers. You can therefore display your products to these audiences, which are similar to your clientele.&nbsp;Last but not least,&nbsp;the cost&nbsp;is also typically&nbsp;lower&nbsp;than Google&#39;s!]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[advertising_marketing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.3.4]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.1.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[79.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[89.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[74.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Oфициальный cоздатель модулей"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges></module><module><id><![CDATA[24239]]></id><name><![CDATA[facebookproductsfeed]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Фиды продуктов: динамическая реклама и маркировка]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Платная поисковая оптимизация]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Только для Facebook и Instagram. Экспортируйте свой каталог продуктов в Facebook, чтобы создавать динамическую рекламу продуктов. Самая эффективная функция ремаркетинга Facebook]]></description><author><![CDATA[Smart Modules]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/sea-paid-search-engine-advertising/24239--.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/24239.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Только для Facebook и Instagram. Экспортируйте свой каталог продуктов в Facebook, чтобы создавать динамическую рекламу продуктов. Самая эффективная функция ремаркетинга Facebook. Используйте теги продуктов в Instagram.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[С помощью этого легко настраиваемого модуля вы сможете создавать каталоги продуктов для их дальнейшего использования в Facebookили Instagram.&nbsp;На странице конфигурации вы сможете выбрать несколько опций, чтобы настроить под себя созданные ленты продуктов.&nbsp;После образования каталога продуктов, его можно использовать для создания обычной рекламы или для добавления тегов к постам в Instagram, но лучше всего его использовать с модулем Facebook Conversion Tracking Plus, чтобы получить возможность пользоваться динамической рекламой продуктов.&nbsp;Благодаря модулю "Ленты продуктов для динамической рекламы и теги Instagram", вы сможете экспортировать ваш каталог продуктов в Facebook. Каталог продуктов содержит основную и дополнительную информацию о Ваших товарах, например, их свойства. Он нужен для использования динамической рекламы продуктов.&nbsp;Что такое динамическая реклама продуктов?Это передовая функция для ретаргетинга от Facebook. Автоматически создаваемые рекламные объявления, основанные на поведении и интересах ваших покупателей.&nbsp;Так как объявления создаются динамически для каждого покупателя, кампании требуют намного меньше обслуживания и затрат, но имеют большие показатели конверсии.&nbsp;Как только покупатель приобретает продукт, модули отправляют необходимую информацию для того, чтобы этому покупателю больше не показывалось это объявление (пока он снова не проявит интерес к какому-либо вашему продукту).&nbsp;Что такое теги продуктов в Instagram? Это функция, доступная только для проверенных аккаунтов, которая позволит вам добавлять в ваши публикации в Instagram теги для продуктов из вашего магазина.&nbsp;Легкий в использовании и хорошо документированныйКаждый раздел модуля хорошо документирован. Это означает, что вам не понадобится никакого предыдущего опыта для настройки и работы с модулем.&nbsp;Также существует несколько продвинутых опций, чтобы лучше контролировать создание лент продуктов.&nbsp;Или поэтапное руководство по настройке cron-job (сторонний скрипт для автоматического обновления ленты).&nbsp;ОшибкиТакже модуль будет проверять и уведомлять об ошибках, которые Facebook может найти во время загрузки модуля, облегчая их поиск и исправление.&nbsp;Фильтрация каталоговИногда вам не нужно, чтобы все ваши продукты отображались в рекламных объявлениях. Facebookпредлагает мощные фильтры, чтобы создать наборы продуктов для дальнейшего использования в рекламных кампаниях. Так вы можете исключить из каталога все ненужные в данный момент продукты.Количество наборов продуктов, которые вы можете создать в Facebook, неограниченно, и они не удаляются после каждого автоматического обновления.&nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[advertising_marketing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.6.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[59.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Oфициальный cоздатель модулей"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/781270-pprod/-.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/781270-pbig/-.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[24345]]></id><name><![CDATA[pm_subscription]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Advanced Subscription with automatic recurring payments]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Абонементов (билетов)]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[A new economic model was created few months ago within the world of e-commerce: subscription-based e-commerce]]></description><author><![CDATA[Presta-Module]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/subscription-products/24345-advanced-subscription-with-automatic-recurring-payments.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/24345.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[A new economic model was created few months ago within the world of e-commerce: subscription-based e-commerce. Known mainly in box form, it is reaching and increasing number of sectors: ready-to-wear clothes, cosmetics, food products...]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Are you ready for subscription-based e-commerce?This is a business model that combines e-commerce and subscription retail. So what is the concept really all about? Subscription-based e-commerce is an excellent way for brands and retailers to begin a process of getting to know their clientèle and establish customer loyalty: the real strength of this economic system is simply its powerful ability to generate customer loyalty! Another advantage is that subscription-based e-commerce enables you to benefit from recurring monthly revenue without having to rely on the acquisition of new customers. What's more, subscription-based e-commerce encourages consumers to indulge and to re-purchase your products if they are impressed.It stands to reason that there is no-one more loyal than a customer who pays a subscription, but be careful, there are a few down sides to the subscription nowadays: customers are developing an increasing dislike to being tied in. As a result you have to grant him a great deal of freedom; he must be able to cancel his subscription whenever he sees fit! If at the beginning of the month your customer no longer wishes to receive the product or products for which he has subscribed, it should not have to be delivered nor billed for. Nevertheless, the likelihood that the customer will continue to use the service is much more important than is the case with "traditional" e-commerce! It is the assurance of regular monthly turnover, alongside the ability to manage your stock levels. Our Advanced Subscription module for PrestaShop takes into account all of these precepts and saves you the precious time that would be required to implement them manually. The reason that the paid subscription model is developing so quickly within the area of e-commerce is that retail sites appear to find in it an effective solution by which to counteract one of the main issues that chips away at their profitability: delivery fees Amazon Premium, Fnac Express+, Cdiscount à volonté... Many e-commerce retailers are now launching their own paid subscription services. In order to grasp the reason behind the phenomenon, one need only remember the fact that delivery fees remain the leading cause of abandoned shopping carts and that, on average, a subscribing customer is twice as lucrative as a non-subscribing customer. A few figures to quantify the impact of delivery on e-business: 87% of online shoppers systematically search for a means by which to avoid having to pay shipping fees (searching for a promotional code, addition of a product to the cart...).44% abandon their purchases purely and simply on account of these fees66% switch to a different retail site in search of delivery conditions that are acceptable to them. Converting customers into subscribers enables online retailers to save time and money compared to traditional methods of recovering customers and generating customer loyalty, as it allows you automate part of the customer relationship. This saving can then be allocated to a free delivery service reserved solely for your subscribers, thus eliminating this purchasing deterrent and in turn achieving much greater conversion rates.  Objective: to generate long-term customer loyalty In addition to the appeal of novelty, subscription-based e-commerce represents a formidable double-edged sword for brands that are reliant on distribution networks and that are targeting growth. In actual fact, first and foremost the subscription principle allows retailers to generate recurrent turnover and a stable operating account. Thus, while subscription-based e-commerce may have cut its teeth with samples and travel-sized products, various other products now also appear to lend themselves to the model: in ready-to-wear clothing, cosmetics, culture and leisure, but also products intended for regular consumption such as mineral water or hygiene products (baby nappies for instance).  Optimization of supply and of your logisticsThe subscription enables you to achieve an improved rate of re-purchase, thus allowing you to purchase from your suppliers more efficiently. In fact, our module will enable you to accurately predict which products will sell, in which quantity and at which frequency. ]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[pricing_promotion]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.3.5]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.9]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[499.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[579.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[449.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Oфициальный cоздатель модулей"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/783025-pprod/advanced-subscription-with-automatic-recurring-payments.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/783025-pbig/advanced-subscription-with-automatic-recurring-payments.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[24399]]></id><name><![CDATA[dashbypayment]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Dashboard Transactions by payment means]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Системный журнал]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Boost your store&#39;s performance by adopting profitable payment means which perfectly fit your clients&rsquo; needs!  One of your payment methods no longer works ? Now you don&#39;t have to wait a f]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/dashboards/24399-dashboard-transactions-by-payment-means.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/24399.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Boost your store&#39;s performance by adopting profitable payment means which perfectly fit your clients&rsquo; needs!  One of your payment methods no longer works ? Now you don&#39;t have to wait a few days before realizing it !&nbsp;  Get direct access from your dashboard to your store&rsquo;s payment means statistics. Easily analyze your website business according to your different payment methods and learn how to optimize your sales.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Increase your conversions by gaining a deeper understanding of your payment methods&#39; performance.   Save time by viewing crucial payment method stats all in one table. There&#39;s nothing easier &ndash; you can do it all from your back-office dashboard!   Be proactive to select the payment methods most adapted to your target customer and highlight them on your store&#39;s home page as reassurance and on the purchase funnel.&nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[19.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[23.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[17.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/784999-pprod/dashboard-transactions-by-payment-means.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/784999-pbig/dashboard-transactions-by-payment-means.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[24876]]></id><name><![CDATA[premiumflatrate]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Shipping Premium flat rate and discounts]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Стоимость доставки]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Offer to your customers a shipping &quot;Premium&quot; flat rate! Add an unlimited number of premium flat rate configurations and define it by customer group, carrier, zone and weight/price ranges]]></description><author><![CDATA[Idnovate]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/shipping-costs/24876-shipping-premium-flat-rate-and-discounts.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/24876.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Offer to your customers a shipping &quot;Premium&quot; flat rate! Add an unlimited number of premium flat rate configurations and define it by customer group, carrier, zone and weight/price ranges.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Get a record conversion rate by offering premium delivery&nbsp;The eternal dilemma of the e-commerce retailer: shipping costs are the reason for 50% of abandoned carts, yet, profitability is at stake if you offer free shipping...&nbsp;We have the solution!&nbsp;With the &#39;Shipping Premium Flat Rate&#39; module, you can offer your customers a&nbsp;premium delivery subscription, like that offered by Amazon and other major e-commerce sites.&nbsp;Your customers pay a delivery subscription can then take advantage of free shipping costs or very reasonable prices throughout the entire year of their subscription.&nbsp;In addition to bringing in&nbsp;additional revenue, you will create a&nbsp;long and sustainable relationship&nbsp;with your customers.&nbsp;Build a very strong and long customer loyalty and encourage them to continue buying in your store.Offer a possibility to purchase a shipping &quot;Premium&quot; flat rate like Amazon Premium.Configure the shipments under Premium flat rate according to your needs. Define which shipping costs will you apply to the customers who has bought the Premium flat rate (free or at a lower amount than other customers).Example: Apply to customers with a valid Premium flat rate a 50% discount in shipping cost.Example: Apply free shipping for customers with a valid 1-year Premium flat rate.PrestaShop new 1.7 version compatible. When you upgrade your store, this module will work!&nbsp;This module DOES NOT require a monthly fee or any other fee, you buy it once and you use it without any restrictions.&nbsp;Our guarantees&nbsp;✪&nbsp;We are&nbsp;a PrestaShop Partner agency. All our developers are certified by PrestaShop.✔&nbsp;We can customize the module or make any modifications that you may need. Contact us for a quote.&nbsp;Do you have any questions or concerns? Send us a message! We will happily answer any questions]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[shipping_logistics]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.1.9]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.6.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[59.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[69.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[54.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Best Module Loyalty"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/awards-loyalty.png]]></badge><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge><badge label="Oфициальный cоздатель модулей"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/812497-pprod/shipping-premium-flat-rate-and-discounts.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/812497-pbig/shipping-premium-flat-rate-and-discounts.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[24894]]></id><name><![CDATA[autogoogleplace]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Google Address Autocomplete]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Pегистрации и оформления заказа]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[This module makes it possible to fill, quickly and without any errors, the address field when yours clients are ordering]]></description><author><![CDATA[Malttt]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/registration-ordering-process/24894-google-address-autocomplete.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/24894.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[This module makes it possible to fill, quickly and without any errors, the address field when yours clients are ordering. It automatically suggests the right address, and so improve yours customer&#39;s browsing comfort.&nbsp;An easy way to save time !]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[This module uses Google Map&#39;s API for automatically fill your clients adresses when they register.Increase your turnover, reducing errors and delivery problems.Decrease product returns&#39; number.Improve your user&#39;s experience.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[checkout]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.4.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.6.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[29.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[34.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[27.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge><badge label="Oфициальный cоздатель модулей"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/798639-pprod/google-address-autocomplete.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/798639-pbig/google-address-autocomplete.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[24986]]></id><name><![CDATA[facturare]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Facturare - Persoana Fizica sau Juridica]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Бухгалтерии и выставления счетов]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Facturare - Persoana Fizica sau Juridica Module allows you to add some additional fields on your shop. Utilizatorii isi vor putea face un cont unde pot alege intre persoana fizica sau juridica]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/accounting-invoicing/24986-facturare-persoana-fizica-sau-juridica.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/24986.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Facturare - Persoana Fizica sau Juridica Module allows you to add some additional fields on your shop. Utilizatorii isi vor putea face un cont unde pot alege intre persoana fizica sau juridica.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[This module allows merchants to:add personal/company option for the user;add company name;add company registration number;add company VAT;add company address;add company bank name;add company IBAN;add person ID serial;add person ID number;add person Identification Number ID; RO:Permite utilizatorului sa isi seteze contul ca fiind persoana fizica sau juridica;Permite utilizatorului sa completeze urmatoarele informatii specifice persoanelor juridice: Companie, Reg. Com., CIF, Banca, IBAN, Adresa;Permite utilizatorului sa completeze informatiile specifice persoanelor fizice: serieCI, numar CI, CNP;Este in concordanta cu dispozitiile din Codul fiscal;Usor de instalat.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[billing_invoicing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.9.5]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[59.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/803820-pprod/facturare-persoana-fizica-sau-juridica.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/803820-pbig/facturare-persoana-fizica-sau-juridica.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[25758]]></id><name><![CDATA[seoperformance]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[URL Cleaner - SEO Performance]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Естественная поисковая оптимизация]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Optimize the SEO of your shop in less than 5 minutes!   Easily delete the numbers (IDs) shown in your URLs and optimize your page links, all while improving the SEO of your online store! The structure]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/seo-natural-search-engine-optimization/25758-url-cleaner-seo-performance.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/25758.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Optimize the SEO of your shop in less than 5 minutes!   Easily delete the numbers (IDs) shown in your URLs and optimize your page links, all while improving the SEO of your online store! The structures of your URLs are pre-defined and non-modifiable for you by the module.​  SEO Performance &ndash; URL Cleaner is the only module that doesn&#39;t use overrides, guaranteeing you increased stability and compatibility with other modules, without any modification to the PrestaShop core.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[SEO Performance Module &ndash; URL Cleaner automatically deletes IDs from URLs that PrestaShop creates by default on your product, category, and CMS pages. It creates shorter and more dynamic definitive redirects for your new URLs to optimize your site&#39;s referencing.  &nbsp; &bull;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Improve the positioning of your shop on search engines &nbsp; Improve your search engine ranking by optimizing the URL schemes of your product, category and CMS pages! &nbsp; &nbsp; &bull;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Save time &nbsp; Our module allows you to improve your URLs as simply as possible. Quick, intuitive and easy-to-use interface.  &nbsp; &bull;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; Safely modify your URLs &nbsp; Easily create backups of your old URLs before permanently changing your store&#39;s URLs.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[seo]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.3.8]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.1.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[59.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[69.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[54.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/810412-pprod/url-cleaner-seo-performance.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/810412-pbig/url-cleaner-seo-performance.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[26011]]></id><name><![CDATA[oct8ne]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Oct8ne - Live chat with Coviewer]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Поддержка и онлайн-чат]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Help your customers by showing them images and videos of your products using the coviewer to help them along in the decision making process]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/support-online-chat/26011-oct8ne-live-chat-with-coviewer.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/26011.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Help your customers by showing them images and videos of your products using the coviewer to help them along in the decision making process.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[What does this module brings you?&nbsp;- Real time interaction with your customers- Displays images and videos of your products by chat or by phone- Predict and detect the best time to talk with your visitors- Between 15% and 20% of customers served through Oct8ne end up buying- 70% of clients attended- Reduces cart abandonment by 1/3- Increases average purchase price by 60%&nbsp;&nbsp;Features&nbsp;- Image and video coviewer- Attend your customers from your Smartphone- Predicting customer behavior- Customize the chat box and all messages- Visitor&#39;s contextual information- Add products to customer&#39;s cart- Mobile phone integration- Real time catalog integration- Management of departments- Common answers- Statistics of sessions, products and carts- Support for multiple stores or websites]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.28]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.4.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/815809-pprod/oct8ne-live-chat-with-coviewer.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/815809-pbig/oct8ne-live-chat-with-coviewer.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[26203]]></id><name><![CDATA[faviconotification]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Browser tab notification (Favicon)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[электронные письма и уведомления ]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Decrease the number of you store&#39;s abandoned carts by adding a notification that will appear directly in the customer&#39;s browser]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/emails-notifications/26203-browser-tab-notification-favicon.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/26203.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Decrease the number of you store&#39;s abandoned carts by adding a notification that will appear directly in the customer&#39;s browser.   This module can be installed and configured in just 30 seconds and displays the number of products in a customer&#39;s cart next to your store&#39;s favicon. It&#39;s a discrete and effective nudge to remind users they have a full cart and encourage them to check out!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[The Browser Tab Notification module lets you: &nbsp;Reduce the number of abandons by showing a notification right in the browser&nbsp;Effortlessly increase your store&#39;s conversion rate: with just a click, the module is active, without any effect on theme, design or navigation!]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[emailing]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.7]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.3.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[29.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[34.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[27.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/824350-pprod/browser-tab-notification-favicon.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/824350-pbig/browser-tab-notification-favicon.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[26586]]></id><name><![CDATA[cappasity3d]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Cappasity 3D and 360 Product Viewer]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Показ товаров]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Showcase your product in 3D with the most powerful 3D platform on the market]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop Partners]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/visual-products/26586-cappasity-3d-and-360-product-viewer.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/26586.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Showcase your product in 3D with the most powerful 3D platform on the market. Create your own 3D Views with the free Cappasity solution using just a regular camera and embed 3D views into your online store.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Let your customers interact with your products in 3D exactly the same way as in the physical store. With 3D they can look at your product from all sides to see details and gain confidence in their purchase. Such immersive shopping experience is essential for e-commerce and results in higher conversion and lower returns.&nbsp;3D Views are proven to increase engagement and conversion over static images by up to 30%!&nbsp;Cappasity solution is a powerful tool for capturing reflective or sparkling objects and demonstrating the textures of your products to potential customers.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.5.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.6.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[0]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[0]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[0]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/832499-pprod/cappasity-3d-and-360-product-viewer.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/832499-pbig/cappasity-3d-and-360-product-viewer.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[26784]]></id><name><![CDATA[todolist]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[To Do List (in your back office)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Системный журнал]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Access all of your tasks directly from your store&#39;s dashboard!   No need for multiple programs anymore: the To Do List module is now included in your back office and lets you create, edit, priorit]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/dashboards/26784-to-do-list-in-your-back-office.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/26784.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Access all of your tasks directly from your store&#39;s dashboard!   No need for multiple programs anymore: the To Do List module is now included in your back office and lets you create, edit, prioritize, and select categories for your tasks so you can save time!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[The To Do List module by PrestaShop allows you to:View all the actions to complete for your store right from your dashboard, without the need for another applicationPrioritize your tasks according to each action&#39;s urgencySave time and increase productivity by sorting tasks (orders in progress, inventory to fill, discounts to manage, etc.)Create tasks with just a click&nbsp;Access a list of what has been done by viewing finished tasks in another tabAssign tasks to any person with an employee account on your store&#39;s back office]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[29.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[34.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[27.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/838558-pprod/to-do-list-in-your-back-office.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/838558-pbig/to-do-list-in-your-back-office.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[26817]]></id><name><![CDATA[prestabay]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[PrestaBay — eBay Marketplace Integration]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Торговая площадка]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[PrestaBay is high-end ebay native integration solution for your store. Inventory Control, Order Management, 22 ebay Marketplaces, Flexible ebay Category Mapping, Real Time ultra fast synchronization]]></description><author><![CDATA[Involic ]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/marketplaces/26817-prestabay-ebay-marketplace-integration.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/26817.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[PrestaBay is high-end ebay native integration solution for your store. Inventory Control, Order Management, 22 ebay Marketplaces, Flexible ebay Category Mapping, Real Time ultra fast synchronization. &nbsp;&nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[PrestaBay eBay Integration is fully integrated PrestaShop backend with eBay marketplaces around the globe. Manage all your inventories, orders and customers managed literally from one page.&nbsp;Power at your fingertips &mdash; get full control on your data with completely customizable solutionBuild on experience &mdash; more than 6 years on market to provide best integration experience.Available worldwide &mdash; send you product on any of 22 available marketplaces and ship it using &nbsp;&#39;Global Shipping&#39; programReal Time &mdash; automatic synchronization with cron job guarantee that you do not miss any ebay salesUltra Fast &mdash; special flash actions allow updating more than 30000 products just in 10 minutesHelp right around the corner &mdash; we are doing our best to provide best customer service as possible, send your support request in your will get response in next 24 hours&nbsp;]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[market_place]]></tab><version><![CDATA[3.1.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[199.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[224.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[179.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge><badge label="Oфициальный cоздатель модулей"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/839014-pprod/prestabay-ebay-marketplace-integration.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/839014-pbig/prestabay-ebay-marketplace-integration.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[26835]]></id><name><![CDATA[buylater]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Wishlist Buy Later ]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Список желаний и Подарочный купон]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[A major feature of large e-commerce sites, adding the &quot;Buy Later&rdquo; (save the product for later) feature to your shopping cart summary is a must to improve your sales and conversion rate]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/wishlist-gift-card/26835-wishlist-buy-later-.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/26835.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[A major feature of large e-commerce sites, adding the &quot;Buy Later&rdquo; (save the product for later) feature to your shopping cart summary is a must to improve your sales and conversion rate.  &nbsp; With one click (much faster than a wishlist), your customers can set aside their impulse buy products and buy them with a later order.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Improve the user experience by offering a feature loved by the customers of the biggest e-commerce sites (Amazon, etc.) on your shopping cart summary;&nbsp;Increase your customers&rsquo; average basket: they forgot this impulse buy that they had set aside during a previous visit, but this time they will add it even though it wasn&#39;t their original purpose;&nbsp;Improve the shopping cart summary by letting your customers list their favorite products and set them aside;&nbsp;Boost your sales by letting them find these items on a future visit and slip them in their shopping cart;&nbsp;Retain your customers by letting them set aside a product they like for their next order;&nbsp;Encourage impulse purchases by indicating when these products are on sale or when their inventory is low]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.1.7]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[69.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[79.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[64.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/839317-pprod/wishlist-buy-later-.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/839317-pbig/wishlist-buy-later-.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[26876]]></id><name><![CDATA[topbanner]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Top Banner]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Блоки, вкладки и Баннеры]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[With the Top Banner module, increase the impact of your sales, special offers and generate more revenue by showing a sales incentive banner with a countdown on all of your site&rsquo;s pages! &nbsp; C]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/blocks-tabs-banners/26876-top-banner.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/26876.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[With the Top Banner module, increase the impact of your sales, special offers and generate more revenue by showing a sales incentive banner with a countdown on all of your site&rsquo;s pages! &nbsp; Communicate easily and effectively to all of your visitors throughout their purchase journey with a custom display and message for your banners.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Highlight your sales codes and make your promotions, sales, and flash sales a successNearly 60% of internet users will abandon their purchase if they can&rsquo;t find a sales code (Mailorama study). Thanks to your sales banner, your customers won&#39;t miss a sale, improving their overall buying experience. &nbsp;Communicate with your visitors and customers easily and effectivelyThe banner is the ideal way of communicating with your users when launching a new collection, announcing a special offer, or during not-to-miss events (Christmas, Black Friday, etc.). &nbsp;Boost your conversions and your earningsBy making sure that your message and inciting items (sales codes, timer, etc.) is shown on the banner that is always displayed on your site, your customers are encouraged to complete their purchases before the end of the sales offer.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.1.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[59.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/896453-pprod/top-banner.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/896453-pbig/top-banner.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[26877]]></id><name><![CDATA[seoimg]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[SEO Image]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Естественная поисковая оптимизация]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Image descriptions are a little-known SEO feature for product pages, but precise description is a surefire way to increase your e-commerce&rsquo;s search engine visibility]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/seo-natural-search-engine-optimization/26877-seo-image.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/26877.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Image descriptions are a little-known SEO feature for product pages, but precise description is a surefire way to increase your e-commerce&rsquo;s search engine visibility. &nbsp;  The SEO Images (Alt tag) module automates ALT tag creation for product images and produces quality content to improve your site&rsquo;s page ranking.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Save time on SEO and start taking advantage of image SEO with automatic rewriting of your ALT tags! &nbsp; With the SEO Images (Alt tag) module:Increase your search engine ranking&nbsp;Increase sales exponentially through improved visibility of your product pages&nbsp;Increase conversion rates with high-quality traffic&nbsp;Set yourself apart from the competition with different SEO image rules for each image]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[seo]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.5]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[59.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[69.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[54.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/840258-pprod/seo-image.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/840258-pbig/seo-image.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[26950]]></id><name><![CDATA[amppages]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[PROFESSIONAL AMP PAGES - ACCELERATED MOBILE PAGES]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Повышения эффективности сайта]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[The First AMP module built for PrestaShop is finally on Add-ons. Over 80 prebuilt features. 100% Template Independent - will work with any template used]]></description><author><![CDATA[Teapot Creative]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/website-performances/26950-professional-amp-pages-accelerated-mobile-pages.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/26950.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[The First AMP module built for PrestaShop is finally on Add-ons. Over 80 prebuilt features. 100% Template Independent - will work with any template used. 7X times faster Mobile Page based on Google's AMP project.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[ You've always been wondering how to create efficient and straightforward mobile page. If you're checking this module, it means that you already know that more than 60% of your customers are coming from a Mobile device, the problem is always how to turn them to buyers or customers. Speed and functionality (simplicity is the key), have always been the two major factors when it comes to sales. We tend to overcomplicate things, and we forget that people checking stuff on mobile are time-dependent, they need the essentials, and motivation to make the purchase. What will this module offer you:  1. Seven times faster mobile page - no more VPS or Dedicated server is needed to have a quick Mobile version. Google caches the mobile result, and it's served to your customer at a ridiculous speed - It's almost Instant2.Boost your mobile results into the TOP placements in Google Mobile Search.3. Significantly higher conversion rate.4. We know that templates are always an issue, so we created one for you for free.5. We created 3 category and product page types, which allows you to conduct A/B tests based on Google Optimize.6. We have the most fantastic support out there, and we continuously develop our module. Our Goal is to offer you the most comprehensive AMP theme and Module out there.7.  Google Already announced that he's testing the AMP version on Tablets. Stay tuned to the new demands.8. Over 500 stores are using this module already ]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.1.3]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.6.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[89.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[104.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[84.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Oфициальный cоздатель модулей"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/1318323-pprod/professional-amp-pages-accelerated-mobile-pages.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/1318323-pbig/professional-amp-pages-accelerated-mobile-pages.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[27274]]></id><name><![CDATA[pscookiebanner]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Cookie Banner + CMS]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Администрация]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/legal/27274-cookie-banner-cms.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/27274.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.9]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[44.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[39.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/873820-pprod/cookie-banner-cms.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/873820-pbig/cookie-banner-cms.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[27535]]></id><name><![CDATA[psproductstats]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Essential Product Statistics]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Статистика и анализ]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[See key statistics for all your product pages, get marketing ideas and optimization tips to improve product performance and boost your sales, all with just a glance!]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/analytics-statistics/27535-essential-product-statistics.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/27535.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[See key statistics for all your product pages, get marketing ideas and optimization tips to improve product performance and boost your sales, all with just a glance!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[With the Product Advanced Stats (Analytics &amp; Tips)&nbsp;module developed by PrestaShop, you can view all of the following for the time period of your choice: &nbsp; Information about sales and revenue generated by the product:A visual representation of your sales curveGross revenue generatedNet revenue generatedBuyer profile bySexAgeCountryPayment preferencesShipping preferences&nbsp; Compare this product&rsquo;s performance with other products in the same category for the designated period with respect to theNumber of products soldEarningsVisits and conversion rate (through Google Analytics)Cart abandonmentRefund rate]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[analytics_stats]]></tab><version><![CDATA[2.0.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.1.1]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[59.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[69.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[54.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/880939-pprod/essential-product-statistics.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/880939-pbig/essential-product-statistics.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[27562]]></id><name><![CDATA[pshomeslider]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Home Slider]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Слайдеров (карусельных) и галерей]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Communicate effectively to all of your visitors by displaying a full screen and responsive slider on your homepage with the Homepage Slider developed by PrestaShop! &nbsp; With a customizable slider i]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/sliders-galleries/27562-home-slider.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/27562.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Communicate effectively to all of your visitors by displaying a full screen and responsive slider on your homepage with the Homepage Slider developed by PrestaShop! &nbsp; With a customizable slider in just a few minutes, modernize the display of your homepage and capture immediately the attention of your visitors as soon as they arrive on your online store!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Modernize and enrich your homepage while keeping a simple design by presenting all of your important contents on a slider in the format and style of your choice.&nbsp;Highlight your desired information and run successfully your marketing campaigns.&nbsp;Whether it is the launch of new products, a special offer or the announcement of upcoming events, the slider allows you to maximize the visibility of your messages on the homepage and to encourage visitors to discover your content.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[slideshows]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.1.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[39.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[44.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[39.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/884765-pprod/home-slider.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/884765-pbig/home-slider.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[28056]]></id><name><![CDATA[bmsprocurement]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[PrestaShop ERP - Purchase Order management]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Соединение с внешней программой (CRM, ERP...)]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Procurement is a PrestaShop ERP&#39;s module&nbsp;providing the features to run your supply orders such as suppliers management, supply orders creation and tracking, calculation of the stock needs]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop ERP]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/third-party-data-integrations-crm-erp/28056-prestashop-erp-purchase-order-management.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/28056.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Procurement is a PrestaShop ERP&#39;s module&nbsp;providing the features to run your supply orders such as suppliers management, supply orders creation and tracking, calculation of the stock needs.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Take advantage of Procurement to optimize your stock by preventing your need and running your supply purchases and your suppliers. &nbsp;PrestaShop ERP&#39;s Procurement allows you to:Prevent out-of-stock productsBe aware of your stock levelsManage product quantities and purchase priceRun your suppliersCreate and track supply ordersReceive supply orders]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[export]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.1.21]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[249.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[289.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[224.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/1044661-pprod/prestashop-erp-purchase-order-management.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/1044661-pbig/prestashop-erp-purchase-order-management.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[28768]]></id><name><![CDATA[psgiftcards]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Premium Gift Card 1.6 - 1.7]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Список желаний и Подарочный купон]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Double your customers and boost your reputation effortlessly with gift cards! Let your customers offer the perfect gift with Premium Gift Cards, designed for you by PrestaShop]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/wishlist-gift-card/28768-premium-gift-card-16-17.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/28768.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Double your customers and boost your reputation effortlessly with gift cards! Let your customers offer the perfect gift with Premium Gift Cards, designed for you by PrestaShop.  Practical and easy to use, gift cards are customers&rsquo; favorite gifts because they are sure to please while letting their recipients choose what they want on your shop!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[One sale = Two customers! The person who buys the gift card, and the one who receives it. With this module, offer gift cards in the amount of your choice that your customers can buy to give to their loved ones, who will use them on your store. This ideal gift is perfect for all sectors of activity (fashion, high-tech, beauty, sport, travel, etc.) and meets all expectations, whatever the occasion.  The Premium Gift Card allows you to:Acquire new customers at a very low cost: gift card recipients represent a significant source of new prospects who may become loyal users;&nbsp;Increase your sales: gift cards are a vital source of additional turnover because recipients often spend more than the amount of the card;&nbsp;Invest in your store&rsquo;s image: by creating a win/win relationship with your users, you improve your customers&rsquo; satisfaction while setting you apart from your competitors;&nbsp;Encourage undecided customers to buy: by offering a risk-free gift adapted to all target audiences, you meet the needs of all your customers, even the most undecided.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.8]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[89.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[104.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[84.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/927393-pprod/premium-gift-card-16-17.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/927393-pbig/premium-gift-card-16-17.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[28845]]></id><name><![CDATA[totalsavings]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Total Savings]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Акции и Подарки]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/promotions-gifts/28845-total-savings.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/28845.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[pricing_promotion]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.5]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[29.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[34.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[27.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/935453-pprod/total-savings.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/935453-pbig/total-savings.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[29193]]></id><name><![CDATA[totcustomfields]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Advanced Custom Fields : create new fields quickly]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Дополнительной информации и вкладок товара]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[This module allows you to create your custom fields and to show them on Product, Category or Order pages in Back Office and Front Office]]></description><author><![CDATA[202 ecommerce]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/product-tab/29193-advanced-custom-fields-create-new-fields-quickly.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/29193.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[This module allows you to create your custom fields and to show them on Product, Category or Order pages in Back Office and Front Office. 4 types of fields are available : text, text area, image, video.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Accelerate your web site development: no need to write dozens of lines of code for adding a custom field in PrestaShop. Create your new custom fields for a few minutes and display them on your product, category or order pages.The module configuration is simple: whether you are a beginner or an expert, this module has been developed to meet a multiple uses. The configuration of the module is simple for people without programming&nbsp;languages knowledge.&nbsp;&nbsp;How does it work?create a new field via module configurations;fill this field via Product, Category or Order pages (depending on your custom field location) in Back Office;show the corresponding value in the Front Office.&nbsp;and that is not all!&nbsp;3 locations are available : Product, Category or Order page (more than 10 native hooks and specific shortcodes for every field for &quot;smarty&quot; display);every field that you create can be required or optional;add instructions for showing your colleagues more information about new fields;you can choose one of 4 types of fields:&nbsp;- text: simple text or phone number,&nbsp;- text area: text only, HTML allowed, WYSIWYG editor,&nbsp;- image: you can upload different format of images : .png, .jpeg, gif. For showing it in the Front Office you can indicate a custom size&nbsp;or use recommended by Prestashop dimensions (for example: large_default (800x800 px) or category_default (141x180 px) etc),&nbsp;- video: integrate video from YouTube;if you want to show the same value you can indicate a default value: it fills automatically every field in Back Office. The default value will be shown on every page in the Front Office;every field could be translatable;you can not only create but also edit, disable or delete created custom fields;view the summary by product, category and order pages : the list of already filled fields is available via Back Office menu: you can access directly to the corresponding page for changing value.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[89.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[104.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[84.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Best Module Innovation"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/awards-innovation.png]]></badge><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge><badge label="Oфициальный cоздатель модулей"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/module-editor.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/955376-pprod/advanced-custom-fields-create-new-fields-quickly.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/955376-pbig/advanced-custom-fields-create-new-fields-quickly.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[29204]]></id><name><![CDATA[bmsorderpreparation]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[PrestaShop ERP - Order Preparation]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Управление заказами]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Order Preparation is a PrestaShop ERP&rsquo;s module made in partnership with Boost my Shop]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop ERP]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/order-management/29204-prestashop-erp-order-preparation.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/29204.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Order Preparation is a PrestaShop ERP&rsquo;s module made in partnership with Boost my Shop. It provides advanced features to fulfill orders by picking, packing and shipping the sold items using a barcode scanner and a picking list.&nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[The order picking tool will allow you to significantly optimize the shipping time while reducing the risk of error (sending unpaid order, wrong product ...).]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.12]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.1.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[249.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[289.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[224.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/1044660-pprod/prestashop-erp-order-preparation.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/1044660-pbig/prestashop-erp-order-preparation.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[32161]]></id><name><![CDATA[psagechecker]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Age Verification Popup]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Безопасности и доступа]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/website-security-access/32161-age-verification-popup.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/32161.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[59.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/1028767-pprod/age-verification-popup.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/1028767-pbig/age-verification-popup.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[32191]]></id><name><![CDATA[shoptermsit]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Custom Terms and Conditions for Italy - GDPR Compliant Module]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Администрация]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Protect yourself against any dispute with&nbsp;Custom terms and conditions adapted to your activity and GDPR compliant !  Customize and update the B to C Custom Terms and Conditions&nbsp;of your onlin]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/legal/32191-custom-terms-and-conditions-for-italy-gdpr-compliant-module.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/32191.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Protect yourself against any dispute with&nbsp;Custom terms and conditions adapted to your activity and GDPR compliant !  Customize and update the B to C Custom Terms and Conditions&nbsp;of your online store using the template created by a&nbsp;law firm specializing in Internet law&nbsp;in collaboration with PrestaShop and protect yourself against any dispute!  This module will take the new General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) into account as soon it come into force the 25th of may 2018.&nbsp;Buy this module right now, and you will benefit of the new Customs Terms GDPR compliant.&nbsp;Only a few clicks will be necessary the 25th of may to upgrade this module into compliance for free.  This module is available for&nbsp;merchants subject to VAT located in Italy ONLY.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Right to data portability, right to access or right to obtain erasure of the personal data, &hellip; &nbsp;All of these subjects are now enforced by the european regulation (General Data Protection Regulation). Starting from the 25th of may 2018 and the entry in force of the GDPR,&nbsp;every e-merchant have to update the Terms and Conditions&nbsp;of his shop to include news specificities for personal data protection of his clients.&nbsp;Your PrestaShop Custom Terms and Conditions allow you to alleviate customer disputes and to comply with the recommendations of the DGCCRF and the CNIL, which ensures you a serene operation of your online store while strengthening the confidence of your customers.  This offer includes a 15-page guide including:The Custom terms and conditions for online marketing to be adapted according to your activity with the recommendations made by a specialized law firmA template of mandatory &quot;terms and conditions&quot; in HTML and PDF format to be inserted directly on your website.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[89.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[104.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[84.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/1029250-pprod/custom-terms-and-conditions-for-italy-gdpr-compliant-module.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/1029250-pbig/custom-terms-and-conditions-for-italy-gdpr-compliant-module.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[32219]]></id><name><![CDATA[pssitemap]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Sitemap Generator for SEO (XML & HTML)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Естественная поисковая оптимизация]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/seo-natural-search-engine-optimization/32219-sitemap-generator-for-seo-xml-html.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/32219.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[seo]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.1.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[79.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[89.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[74.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/1031595-pprod/sitemap-generator-for-seo-xml-html.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/1031595-pbig/sitemap-generator-for-seo-xml-html.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[32356]]></id><name><![CDATA[shoptermsuk]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Custom Terms and Conditions for United Kingdom- GDPR Compliant Module]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Администрация]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Protect yourself against any dispute with&nbsp;Custom terms and conditions adapted to your activity and GDPR compliant !  Customize and update the B to C Custom Terms and Conditions&nbsp;of your onlin]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/legal/32356-custom-terms-and-conditions-for-united-kingdom-gdpr-compliant-module.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/32356.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Protect yourself against any dispute with&nbsp;Custom terms and conditions adapted to your activity and GDPR compliant !  Customize and update the B to C Custom Terms and Conditions&nbsp;of your online store using the template created by a&nbsp;law firm specializing in Internet law&nbsp;in collaboration with PrestaShop and protect yourself against any dispute!  This module will take the new General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) into account as soon it come into force the 25th of may 2018.&nbsp;Buy this module right now, and you will benefit of the new Customs Terms GDPR compliant.&nbsp;Only a few clicks will be necessary the 25th of may to upgrade this module into compliance for free.  This module is available for&nbsp;merchants subject to VAT located in the United Kingdom ONLY.]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Right to data portability, right to access or right to obtain erasure of the personal data, &hellip; &nbsp;All of these subjects are now enforced by the european regulation (General Data Protection Regulation). Starting from the 25th of may 2018 and the entry in force of the GDPR,&nbsp;every e-merchant have to update the Terms and Conditions&nbsp;of his shop to include news specificities for personal data protection of his clients.&nbsp;Your PrestaShop Custom Terms and Conditions allow you to alleviate customer disputes and to comply with the recommendations of the DGCCRF and the CNIL, which ensures you a serene operation of your online store while strengthening the confidence of your customers.  This offer includes a 15-page guide including:The Custom terms and conditions for online marketing to be adapted according to your activity with the recommendations made by a specialized law firmA template of mandatory &quot;terms and conditions&quot; in HTML and PDF format to be inserted directly on your website.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.0]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.5.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[119.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[134.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[109.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/1035246-pprod/custom-terms-and-conditions-for-united-kingdom-gdpr-compliant-module.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/1035246-pbig/custom-terms-and-conditions-for-united-kingdom-gdpr-compliant-module.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[32549]]></id><name><![CDATA[advancedstock]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[PrestaShop ERP - Advanced Stock]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[запасов и поставщиков]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Advanced Stock is a PrestaShop ERP&#39;s module providing the features to manage your stocks in different warehouses, edit stock levels using a barcode scanner or register stock movements in your back]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop ERP]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/stock-supplier-management/32549-prestashop-erp-advanced-stock.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/32549.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Advanced Stock is a PrestaShop ERP&#39;s module providing the features to manage your stocks in different warehouses, edit stock levels using a barcode scanner or register stock movements in your back office.&nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Gain in productivity and save time in your stock management by managing stock movements and changes and the activity list of these.  PrestaShop ERP&#39;s Advanced Stock allows you to:Register stock movements from a warehouse to another oneSet attributes for each one of your warehouses : name, address, opening hours, status,...Keep an activity list of movements Be aware of your stock levels]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[administration]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.5]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[249.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[289.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[224.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Official Partner"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-official-partner.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/1050753-pprod/prestashop-erp-advanced-stock.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/1050753-pbig/prestashop-erp-advanced-stock.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[41139]]></id><name><![CDATA[psbuybutton]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Buy Button Premium (Blog & SEO)]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Блог, форумов и новостей]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/blog-forum-news/41139-buy-button-premium-blog-seo.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/41139.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[content_management]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[99.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[114.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[89.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/1293753-pprod/buy-button-premium-blog-seo.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/1293753-pbig/buy-button-premium-blog-seo.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[41336]]></id><name><![CDATA[pscustomblock]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Custom Block Homepage]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Блоки, вкладки и Баннеры]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Optimize your homepage design and display by adding image and text blocks that can easily be customized in just a few clicks! &nbsp; Using the Bloc Custom Homepage module, make your page more attracti]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/blocks-tabs-banners/41336-custom-block-homepage.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/41336.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Optimize your homepage design and display by adding image and text blocks that can easily be customized in just a few clicks! &nbsp; Using the Bloc Custom Homepage module, make your page more attractive and effective with your own brand identity and entice your visitors the moment they enter your online store!]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Draw the attention of your visitors as soon as they enter your store. An Internet user spends just 3 seconds on average to decide whether to stay on a website, and 8 seconds to perform an action. Make the best possible impression on your new visitors and lower the bounce rate of your website!&nbsp;Enhance your homepage and boost whatever makes your store special.&nbsp;The homepage is your online store front. It must highlight the things that differentiate you from your competitors. With our Bloc Custom Homepage module, you can display all the essential information that you want to highlight in image and text blocks, while keeping your design clean and simple.&nbsp;Entice potential customers and boost your conversion rate. According to a Stanford survey, 75% of all Internet users admit to judging a company&rsquo;s credibility on the design of its website. Make your website look professional to strengthen the bond of trust between your company and consumers and encourage them to discover your contents, make a purchase or contact you.]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[59.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/1287094-pprod/custom-block-homepage.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/1287094-pbig/custom-block-homepage.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[41453]]></id><name><![CDATA[psmassedit]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Product Bulk Edit]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Быстрое & массовое редактирование]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/mass-updates/41453-product-bulk-edit.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/41453.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[quick_bulk_update]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.3]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[59.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[69.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[54.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/1287690-pprod/product-bulk-edit.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/1287690-pbig/product-bulk-edit.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[41875]]></id><name><![CDATA[spmgsnipreview]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Product, Shop Reviews, Reminder, Profile, Rich Snippets]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Отзывы клиентов]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[Best "Conversion rates" module on prestashop awards 2019! Increase conversion, traffic, visibility in the Google search results: Highly flexible module]]></description><author><![CDATA[Community developer]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/customer-reviews/41875-product-shop-reviews-reminder-profile-rich-snippets.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/41875.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[Best "Conversion rates" module on prestashop awards 2019! Increase conversion, traffic, visibility in the Google search results: Highly flexible module. Also, it's not all, module include Google Product Review Feeds for Google Shopping. ]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Increase conversion, traffic, visibility in the Google search results: Highly flexible module Product, Shop Reviews, Reminder, Profile, Rich Snippets. Also, it's not all, module include Google Product Review Feeds for Google Shopping. Read below about all available functions&nbsp;General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)&nbsp;- Compliant with PrestaShop’s Official GDPR Compliance Module&nbsp; ]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.6.1]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.6.0.4]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.6.0]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[49.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[59.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[44.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Best Module Conversions"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/awards-toconvert.png]]></badge><badge label="PrestaShop&#39;s Favorite"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/ps-selected.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/1293185-pprod/product-shop-reviews-reminder-profile-rich-snippets.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias3.prestastore.com/1293185-pbig/product-shop-reviews-reminder-profile-rich-snippets.jpg]]></big></cover></module><module><id><![CDATA[41931]]></id><name><![CDATA[pscartdropdown]]></name><displayName><![CDATA[Cart Dropdown]]></displayName><categoryName><![CDATA[Меню]]></categoryName><description><![CDATA[The Cart Dropdown module allows you to configure a cart dropdown in order to optimize the user experience for your customers and prompt them to finalize their order]]></description><author><![CDATA[PrestaShop]]></author><url><![CDATA[https://addons.prestashop.com/ru/menu/41931-cart-dropdown.html?utm_source=back-office&utm_medium=push-addons&utm_campaign=back-office-RU&utm_content=download]]></url><img><![CDATA[https://medias1.prestastore.com/img/pico/41931.jpg]]></img><description_full><![CDATA[The Cart Dropdown module allows you to configure a cart dropdown in order to optimize the user experience for your customers and prompt them to finalize their order. &nbsp; This cart summary appears when the mouse is hovered over it and can redirect your customers directly to the first step of the purchase funnel for a better conversion rate.&nbsp;]]></description_full><additional_description><![CDATA[Boost your conversion rate: According to Sale Cycle, 74% of your site&rsquo;s visitors will abandon their cart without pressing the order button. Make it easier for them to access this button by showing the Order button in your dropdown menu so that they can complete their order more quickly.&nbsp;  23% of shoppers abandon a cart simply because they do not have a clear idea of the total amount of an order while shopping. With our Cart Dropdown module, your customers can view their cart in advance when they want to know their price, on any page, they visit.&nbsp;&nbsp;Offer a better customer experience:Being able to check their cart summary from any page without exiting their navigation gives customers peace of mind. This cart dropdown has been designed to respond to customer mouse movements in order to prevent frustration]]></additional_description><tab><![CDATA[front_office_features]]></tab><version><![CDATA[1.0.2]]></version><compatibility><from><![CDATA[1.7.0.0]]></from><to><![CDATA[1.7.5.2]]></to></compatibility><price><EUR><![CDATA[29.99]]></EUR><USD><![CDATA[34.99]]></USD><GBP><![CDATA[27.99]]></GBP></price><badges><badge label="Made by PrestaShop"><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/themes/prestastore/img/front/sprites/badges/made-by-prestashop.png]]></badge></badges><cover><small><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/1293840-pprod/cart-dropdown.jpg]]></small><big><![CDATA[https://medias2.prestastore.com/1293840-pbig/cart-dropdown.jpg]]></big></cover></module></modules>